To help us make our outlook pretty.
We're going to use the Bouma library, so I'm going to jump to Boma dot IO.
Now this isn't a access course, so I won't be focusing on Boma and CC too much.
We're just simply using it to help us make our look pretty without having to spend tons of time writing.
And that way we can purely focus on Vue.js three on the composition API.
Also, I'm not necessarily suggesting that you should use Boma for your projects.
You should make an informed choice based on your individual projects needs.
However, I believe Boma is currently the third most popular CC framework.
After Bootstrap and Tailwind CC.
However, I've chosen BOMA for this project because it's the easiest CSA framework to get started with
and it has all of the components that we're going to need for this project.
So if I jump to documentation on components, we have this card component that we're going to use,
this KNOP component that we're going to use, the modal component that we're going to use.
And it has a bunch of farm components that we're going to use like this input.
And it also has a nice button component that we're going to use as well.
So let's get Boma installed to our project.
So I'm going to jump to overview and then start scroll down and there's a few ways we can install it.
We can install it using a CD link where it will be loading in externally, or we can download it from
GitHub or we can install the NPM package.
And this is the way I'm going to do it.
So we need to run NPM, install BOMA, so let's copy that.
Open up our terminal, kill the dev process and run NPM, install BOMA that's installed.
And if we jump to our node modules folder, we can see Boma is here and if we open the CSC folder,
we can see up all the access files.
I'm going to use the minified version bulma documents.
SS But we can also use the own minified version for modok costs.
So I'm going to right click on board the document.
SS Click on copy paste.
That.
I'm going to jump to The View.
I'm going to add a style tag.
And to import that CSV file I'm going to add at import and then I'll paste in that path.
We have the full path on my computer here.
But we only need the path from this Bournemouth of all here.
So I'll remove everything before that.
The folder and we need to add a semicolon at the end.
Let's say that we need to relaunch our up.
So let's run NPM, run depth, jump back to our app.
Now we can see our styles have already changed a little bit, but just to make sure Obama is working
less out of class to each of our routes, a link components here of button and this should give these
a nice button style.
Save that.
And yet we can see some nice little buttons now.
We can now start using Burma to make our outlook beautiful.