Let's add a nice, beautiful number to our app.
Now, first of all, let's just create a component for it which will import into view.
And for some reason my components folder has disappeared.
But you should have a components folder here.
I'm going to create the components inside that.
I'm going to create a folder called layout.
And I don't like the way these code groups are folders together like this by default.
So I'm just going to fix up my going to code and preferences and settings and I going to search for
compact.
Now we can just uncheck this compact folders option and we now have a normal folder system here.
So inside the layout folder, I'm going to create a file called NAV Bar Dot View and for now we'll just
start our template tags just out of Dave with my now bar for the text.
Now let's jump to that view and import this component.
So a lot of our script sets up tags.
I'm going to add a block comment here which just says imports.
And then we'll import not far from slash components, slash, layout, slash, not bar dot view.
And I use these big comments to split up my code into sections.
I just find it makes it a lot easier for me to scan through my code.
Well, this is entirely optional.
You don't need to add these comments if you don't want to.
Now, let's take this not bar component on the page.
So I'm going to get rid of these routes of view length for now and just output on up.
I'll save that.
And yeah, we can see mine up on the page.
So now let's jump to the BOMA site and we're going to go to Components and number.
Scroll down, stretch this out a bit and we're just going to copy this example here for a basic number
and then we're going to modify it.
So I went to copy all of this code, move this back over and then we'll jump soon enough by you, paste
it all in here, indent that save and we can now see.
Now I'll just zoom out a little bit and I want end up lots of nice green color instead of white.
And we can do that by adding a class to this nav element.
Have split the attributes.
I'm not using the split YAML attributes extension which we installed earlier.
A lot of class of is dash success say that we now have a nice green number.
And again, I'm not going to be explaining all of these classes from Boma too much because I want to
stay focused on view on the composition API as much as possible.
But you can find all of these available classes on the app, on the site, for example, for this not
by video down.
Colors shows you how to add all of these different colors here.