Let's customize this number.
First of all, I want to get rid of this more link here with this dropdown.
So let's scroll down the part of view and see if we can find that.
We can see that more link here and we can see this dip for the class of not by item.
Let's collapse that, Dave.
Just get rid of it.
Save that and we see that disappear.
Now let's move these two links over to the right hand side.
So I'm going to scroll up on these two nav item links here when I cut them.
Just get rid of this now.
Bar dash, start dip.
Now we're going to paste those links into this number and dip, which will put them over on the right.
So let's collapse this dip inside that now by item.
Get rid of that.
I'll just paste in the links we caught before.
Save that.
Let's make these links to notes view and our stats view.
So I'm just going to remove the second item and this first one.
I'm going to change this to a roots, a link component.
Make sure we change both the opening and closing text that I'm going to split the attributes on this.
Change the text to notes.
I'm allowed to prop to this route.
So they set that to the path slash, which is where our notes route is that I'll select this route.
So Link duplicates it and we'll change the two prop to the path slash stats.
We'll change the text to stats as well.
Save that.
We now have links to our notes and stats page.
We can see this heading.
Updating.
An owner has a class which is is active which we can add to one of these number items to make it appear
active.
You can see this link now looks active on these routes.
Link components can actually add a class to the link when that link is the active link.
So if I just cut that class, we can just add a prop of active dash class and set it to this class is
active and I'll also copy that and paste it to the stats link.
Say that we should now have active classes on our links.
And yet that's working.
And now let's just replace this Boma logo with a title for our app.
So I'll scroll up to the top.
And inside this SNAP brand div, we have this attack with a class of no item.
I'm going to remove the image that's inside that and remove this hate trap.
I don't want to change this attack into a depth because I don't want this to be a link that inside that
I'll just have the text, no pulse and save that to improve the style of the text here.
I'm going to add a class to this depth of is dash size does fall to make it a bit bigger and that class
of is dash family mono space to give it this mono space style font.
And again, you can find all of these classes on the BOMA site, which is very well documented.