Now, currently the content of this number will keep stretching out as the browser gets wider and wider,
which doesn't look too great, especially on really big screens.
So we have the logo right over here and then these links right over here.
I'd like all this to be constrained in the middle after a certain point, and we can use bonus container
element to do this.
So I'm going to surround everything inside an up with a dev with a class of container.
So I've just minimized everything that's in there and a lot of depth for the class of container to make
sure it constrains once the browser is wider than a certain number of pixels out of class of is dash
max dash desktop.
And these classes are all documented on the bonus site.
And then I'm just going to move this not pop round this not bar menu into that div and save that and
we can now see a larger screen's everything is constrained to the middle of the page.
Now, if our view gets below one or two four pixels, we see the novel length disappear and we see this
little burger icon, but nothing happens when we click it.
That's because in order to show the mobile menu change this icon into its active state, we need to
add a class of is active to both the burger icon and the now menu as well.
This is all documented on the KNOP on the page.
But just to demonstrate this, let's hardcoded those classes in now.
So I'm going to split the attributes on this tag with a class of not pop burger.
I'm going to add a class of is active and save that we can see the icon change to an X and if we scroll
down to this not menu dip, I'll also split the attributes on that.
I'll have the same class to this div.
So is dash active save that we can now see the mobile menu appear.
So let's set up a ref to toggle these classes when we click on the burger menu.
So I'm going to remove these hardcoded classes for now from the top menu diff on the number burger attack.
Say that unless you're down to our script section, which doesn't exist yet, so let's create it.
Script sets up a lot of block comment which says mobile now.
I will set a constant called show mobile now set by equal to a ref with an initial value of false.
So when this is false, we won't show the mobile enough.
When it's true, we will show it and we need to import the ref method from view.
So just going to add a quick comment here.
Imports will import ref from view and save that.
And now let's conditionally add those classes based on this ref.
So let's jump to the burger icon first, which is here.
With a class of not bar dash burger.
Now lets bind to the class attributes by adding colon class curly braces and a lot of class of is dash
active, but only when show mobile nav is true.
And then I'll copy this and also add it to this day with the class enough bar dash menu and I'll save
that.
And now if we jump down to our ref and change the value to true that we can now see the mobile NAV and
the active version of the burger icon.
So let's set that back to false and we'll toggle the value of this ref when we click on the burger menu.
So we'll jump up to.
The nut Bob burger attack an out of click and when we click this we're going to set show mobile now
equal to the opposite of show mobile now.
So if it's false we'll set it to true and if it's true, will set it to false.
And because this is an attack, it's going to try and go somewhere when we click it.
So to stop that from happening, I'm just going to add a modifier of prevent and this will prevent the
default behavior of the element we're clicking on.
The default behavior of an attack is to go to another page.
So let's save that and see if that's working.
Click on the button and we see the mobile number page.
Click it again and we see it disappear.
Now, I don't like the fact that our mobile menu is pushing our page content down.
See how it's pushing this heading now.
I would rather it was just position absolutely over the top of our page.
So let's just add a little bit of style to make that happen.
So let's scroll down to the bottom and I do style tag.
A lot of media query here for mobile.
So media lacks width one, two, three pixels because that's when the mobile nav styles kick in.
When we scale down the browser.
And now we want to target on up menu, which is this step here with the class of up dash menu.
So I'm just going to add dash bar dash menu set up to position absolute and set the left to zero and
set the width to 100%.
Save that click on the button and our mobile menu is now positioned over the top of our content instead
of pushing it down.