Before we start working on the design of our notes page, the main page in our.
First of all, I'd just like to constrain the content of all of our pages and also add a little bit
of padding because right now we can see the content of our pages is right up in the corner with no padding.
And also our content is always right over to the left.
Regardless of how wide browser is, which doesn't look too pretty.
So I'm just going to use the same classes that we use to constrain the content in an upper u container
and max desktop classes.
And so to do this, I'm going to update view and just surround our route to view in a dev with these
classes.
So container and is mux desktop just move the roots of view into that and save that.
We can see our content is now constrained.
Boma has some padding classes we can use to add a little bit of padding around our pages as well.
And these are all documented on the OMA site.
So a lot of class of PDX dash two to add some horizontal padding and then a class of P dash for to add
some vertical padding.
And this is looking good now on smaller screens, on wider screens.
A logo isn't lining up with our content.
I think it would look better if this lined up.
So let's add some padding to our lap bar as well.
So our Johnson up view and then this contain tape that we added and a lot of classic stuff too.
And that's looking pretty good now.
And now let's give all of our pages a little background color, which matches the color of our number.
So I'm going to go to the file Explorer and open up index dot HTML.
I'm going to add a class to a page HTML element and BOMA has tons of color classes we can use and they're
all documented on the for my site.
I'm going to use the class has background dash success dash light and say that we now have this nice
little green color in the background of all of our pages.