Now let's create the design for our notes using bonus card component.
So I'm going to jump on over to the bonus site and go to components on card.
Our full screen, this is EQ.
And I'm going to scroll down to this example here, which has these buttons at the bottom which we can
use to add the ability to edit and delete a note.
So I'm going to copy this example here by clicking on copy, and then I'll jump back to note bubbles.
I'm going to add this to our notes view.
So we're going to go to source views and view notes dot view and I'll paste that inside this diff over
the top of this H1, indent it a little bit and save that and I'm going to get rid of this head at the
top.
So that's this header element here.
So we'll get rid of that, save that.
And I'm just going to enable word by default.
So I'm going to go to code preferences and settings, search for word wrap and set that to on by default.
That's better.
Now I'm going to get rid of everything inside this div with a class of content.
So get rid of that.
Spits out some room by just typing in lower and then hitting enter should see this abbreviation.
Save that.
I'll just get rid of the save button cause we're only going to need an edit on the delete button.
Let's just see how this will look with multiple cards on.
A quick trick to do this is to just add av4 to the parent diff.
So before that we can just do I in three to spit out three of these.
And you can see we need a little bit of space between each note.
So a lot of class to this day for the class of card of and B for margin button dash for save that these
are looking pretty good.
Let's just make sure they look okay on a big screen or on a small screen.
Yeah, pretty good.