That sort of farm to the top of our notes view with a text area and a button that we can use to add
a new note.
So back to the ball, Messi.
I'm going to go too far.
And General, I'm going to scroll down to complete form example, show the code and all I'm going to
grab here is from this text area down to these buttons.
So let's scroll down the code and there's a text area and we do want this did with the class of field
that's around it.
So I'll select from there.
To the step down here with the two buttons inside it.
Copy that.
And we'll paste this above our notes.
Well, still inside this day with the class of notes.
So a paste that here indents it a little bit and save that.
Now I'm going to remove this label here with the text message, which is here.
So get rid of that and I'm going to get rid of this checkbox here.
Does this step here with the class of fields?
So we'll get rid of that.
We'll get rid of these two radio buttons, which is this div here.
Save that.
Now I'm going to surround the text area and the buttons in a card component with a background color.
So I'll stick that up here.
So a lot of tape with the class of card to give it a background color.
Without it, class of has background success dark and I'm going to select these two Davis to the class
of fields cut those paste them inside this div save that we need to add a bit of padding here so a class
of P does for give it a bit padding and we need a bit of margin at the bottom.
So a lot of class and B margin bottom dash five save thought.
Now I'm going to remove this cancel button.
So I'll remove this tape with the class of control which has the console button inside it.
Save that and I want to pull this button over to the right hand side.
You can do that by adding a class of is dash grouped dash right to this day for the class of field save
that I want to change the color and the text of this button is going to break it up onto multiple lines.
I'll change the text inside it to add new notes.
Save that I will change the background color by adding a class of has dash background dash success.
Save that.
I'll finally let's change the placeholder on this text area and in fact I'm going to change this into
a self closing tag like that and split the attributes.
I will set the placeholder to add a new note, save that this is looking pretty good on desktop.
It's looking pretty good on Mobile, too.