Let's add a custom directive to this up.
And one thing we could do is create a custom directive which auto focuses this text area when the page
is loaded so that the user can immediately start typing a new notes without having to click into it.
So first of all, let's just set up a local custom directive inside this add edit note component and
that's in source components notes and at edit notes.
So we'll jump down to the script section and I'll jump down to the bottom.
Let's add a new comment here which says Directives.
So do you remember how we add a local custom directive?
Feel free to pass the video on, see if you can remember how to do it.
But what we do is we create a constant and we need to make sure the name of this constant starts with
a lowercase v and is in common case.
So we could call this v auto focus and we set this equal to an object and we could add any hooks we
want in here, such as created or we're going to use mounted.
And we set this equal to a method like this and we can pass the L parameter in here on this L parameter.
It will give us access to the element once it's mounted, as in the element which we add this v auto
focus directive two.
So we can then just focus it with l dot focus and now we can just add this directive to any focus of
all element that's in this component.
So let's add it to text area which is here.
And remember, we need to change the name that we've used here from camel case into dash case so we
can up this like this v dash auto focus.
Save that.
And if we reload this page, we can see that the text area is automatically focused without us needing
to click into it.
Since this add edit note component is a shared component which is also used on the edit page.
It should also work here as well, which it does.
We can see the text area auto focused here as well.