Now let's say we have an input on our stats page.
Let's jump to the stats page.
So views view stats dot view a collapse table.
I will add an input after this and I'll set the type to text and we'll give this a placeholder.
Do you love note balls?
Save that and jump to our stats page to make this look a bit prettier.
A lot of class of input, which is from Bulma and that's better.
So let's say we also want to auto focus this input when this page has loaded.
Well, that's not currently going to work.
If we add this v auto focus directive here.
Save that and reload.
If we look at our console we can see an error.
Cannot read properties of undefined reading deep.
And that's because this the auto focus doesn't exist within the context of this component view.
Start, stop view.
It only exists on the edit note top view component where we've set it up here.
So let's jump back to view.
Start, stop view.
Remove this the auto focus directive.
Save that and jump back to our notes page and add edit note up view.
Let's make this directive, a global directive that we can use anywhere.
So first of all, let's create a new folder in our source folder where all of our directives can live.
So going to right click the source folder, click on new folder, create a folder called Directives.
And inside that, we're going to create a new file called the Auto Focus.
We might as well give it the same name as our constant name.
Now let's jump to add edit note dot view.
Select this constant and cut it.
Let's also remove this comment and save that.
Now let's jump to our new auto focus file and paste that directive.
And all we need to do is export this so that it can be imported from our components, so we can just
start export like that.
Save that now if we want to add edit knocked out view, we can just import this directive.
So let's jump up to our imports.
We can just do imports.
Curly braces.
The auto focus from slash directives.
Slash the auto focus that I know.
We just need to add the directive to the text area which we already have done.
So this should hopefully be working now and we can see when we reload the page it still auto focuses
the text area, except now it's using this global directive that we created.
So let's use the same global directive on our stats page.
So let's jump to view, start, stop view.
We need to import the directive.
So I'll just jump back to edit note dot view and copy the import statement.
Job to view.
Stop, stop view.
Paste that here.
Save that and we can now use that here as well.
So let's add it to this import we just created.
So V dash auto focus save that reload and we can see this import on the start page is now auto focus
as well.