Lazada watcher to this up.
So let's say on our notes page view notes dot view, we want to watch the number of characters that
are being entered into this text area or in other words, the number of characters in this new note
ref that's on view notes dot view.
And if that gets to 100 characters, we want to show an alert.
So let's add a watcher to do this on View Notes.
W So do you remember how we add a watcher?
That's right.
We first need to import the watch method from view and we then use this watch method.
So at the bottom here, I'm going to add a new comment which says Watch characters and we'll use this
watch method.
And the first parameter is the data that we want to watch and we want to watch this new note ref so
we can just pass in new notes as the first parameter.
The second parameter is a method callback method which will be fired any time this data property that
specified here changes.
If we like, we can pass in the new value on the old value here.
So let's just log these out.
So a log out, new value and then comma u-value then I'll duplicate that I'm a log out old value, save
that reload and if we change the text we can see the old value in the new value always being locked
out.
Now we're not actually going to need the old value here, so I'll get rid of that and get rid of these
logs.
So if the character of this new note ref gets to 100, we're going to show an alert so we can just add
an F statement to do this so we can do if new value length to get the length of the new value is equal
to 100, then we can alert something.
So alert only 100 characters allowed.
Gosh darn it, save that reload.
Just to make it easier to test this, I'm going to jump to the underlying text area which is in source
components notes and add edit note dot view.
And I'm just going to add a max length attribute to this set that to 100.
So I thought, let's test this out.
We can just start typing into this text area.
And when we get to 100 characters, we see the alert so we can see that our watcher is working.