Now let's say we want to have the same watch characters functionality on our stats page on this input.
Well, we could just copy this, watch code, paste it into our stats page views that start view and
then just adjust the data property that we're watching here.
But then we'd be duplicating code.
It'd be better to put this watch into its own composable file, which we can use everywhere.
So let's do that.
Let's jump to our Explorer.
We want to put a composable in a folder called Use Inside the source folder.
So that's right click source and choose new folder.
Create a folder called Use and then inside that will create a new file called Use Watch Characters talks
to set up a composable.
We just need to export a function with the same name as our file.
So use watch characters like this.
Let's jump back to view notes that view.
Just call this watcher.
Jump to our composable and paste that in here.
And actually back on.
Do you notice that view?
We can now remove the watch method that we're importing, saved up and jump back to use watch characters.
And we do need to import this watch method here.
So let's just add import watch from view.
Now, in order to make this composable generic, we need to be able to pass in the data property that
we want to watch as a parameter.
So let's just accept that here.
So we could just call this value to watch or something like that.
Whatever we're passing in here is what we want to watch here.
So let's change new notes to value, to watch and save that.
And now we should be able to use this composable to watch the number of characters of any data property
within our app and then show this alert if it hits 100 characters.
So let's jump to view, note stock view and we need to import this composable.
So imports use watch characters from slash use slash use watch characters save up a stop to our notes
page, jump down to the bottom and we should not be able to use this composable to watch this new note
ref, which is bound to the text area so we can just to use watch characters and then pass in the ref
that we want to watch.
New note.
New notes.
Save that.
Let's see if that still working.
Yep, still working.
And now we should also be able to use the same functionality on our stats page.
So let's jump to our stats page.
Source views view stats dot view.
And again, we need to import this composable.
I'll just copy the import line from view notes dot view paste that here.
We should now be able to use it on the stats page as well.
However, we don't have a data property set up for this import here, so let's just set that up.
So a lot of comment here which says Love Note Balls, I will set up a ref.
So const love note balls equals a ref with an initial value of an empty string.
Now we need to import ref from view.
Let's add that to the top import ref from view.
Now let's bind this ref to the input.
So here's the input side of the model.
Set it to love note balls.
Save that.
Let's just change this default value to see if it's hooked up.
And yep, that's hooked up.
So we should now be able to watch the characters in this input.
So again, we can just to use watch characters pass in the ref that we want to watch, which is love
note balls, love note balls.
Save that and hopefully we should see the same functionality here.
And yeah, it's working.