Let's make use watch characters composable a bit more flexible.
So right now, the alert will always be fired when the length of the characters reaches 100.
But let's say we want to be able to adjust the number of characters at which this fire's, let's say,
on the notes page.
We want to fire this 100 characters.
But on the stats page, in this input, we want to fire this up 50 characters.
Well, we could do this by adding another parameter to use what characters function here.
So let's add a second parameter here called max chars and we can pass the same on.
We use this composable in our components.
So in our if statement here instead of if new value length is equal to 100 or two, if new value dot
length is equal to max chars.
So I'll replace 100 with max chars and we'll also output this number in our alert as well.
So I'll change this to a template string.
So I'll replace the hundred with dollar curly braces.
I will output this max chars.
Let's get this max charles parameter a default value in case it's not been provided.
We can do that by just setting max chars equals to 100 save up.
And since we're not currently providing this Max Charles parameter on the notes page, then this should
just work as it did before by firing the alerts 100 characters.
So let's just test that on yet.
That's still working out 100 characters.
So let's say on our notes page, we just want to use the default functionality with 100 characters.
But on our stats page we want the max chars to be 50 characters.
So let's jump to the stats page and jump to views that stop view.
Let's scroll down to where we're triggering our composable passive in the second parameter of 50.
Now let's save that reload.
This should be firing a little bit sooner now.
50 characters on.
Yeah.
And our alert says only 50 characters allowed.
Gosh darn it.
And so composable is now a lot more flexible and useful.
And of course, we could make it more flexible with additional parameters, etc..
Now, for a simple composable like this, which only contains a watcher, then it makes sense to just
import the composable and just fire the composable function like we're doing here.
But for more complicated composable, which contain a bunch of different things such as data, methods,
computed properties, etc., then it makes more sense to only extract the things that we need from the
composable using restructuring and for a reminder of how we do that with more complex composable as
jump back to module 11, the composable module.