So we've created a custom composable.
But let's also add a composable from the view use library.
And if we look at our mobile menu here currently, the only way we can close this is by clicking on
the X.
We can't close it by clicking outside of it like we would usually expect.
So let's use one of the composable from the view used library to solve this for us.
So let's jump over to view use dot org.
Get started.
We need to install this first.
So let's talk to our terminal killer.
That process will run this command to install.
If you use.
I'm not finished.
So let's relaunch our up with AMPM run death and on The View Use I'm going to go to menu core functions
census how we're going to use this on click outside composable.
So let's click on that.
We can see an example here.
We can open up a model and we can close it with the exporting, but we can also close it by clicking
anywhere outside of the model.
So let's hide the terminal here, close all of our components and open up the number, source components,
layout number.
And let's look at the example code here.
So we need to import the on click outside composable from view use.
So let's copy that line and add that to our import section here.
And we can see in this example here, we need to set up a template ref, add that ref to the element
before we can use this.
So let's find on up menu element which is here this Dave with the classic enough bar menu.
So let's add a rep to this.
We could call this number menu ref or something like that.
Let's jump down to the script section.
A lot of comment here which says Click outside to close.
We need to set up a template ref like we can see in this example here.
So we'll create a constant with the same name as our ref, which is what has it gone now from a new
ref?
So const nav bar menu.
Ref equals a ref with a default value of no.
And now we can use this composable.
So let's copy this line here.
Paste that here.
Change the target to this graph here.
So I'll copy that.
Paste that there.
Save that.
Now let's show the mobile menu.
Clear the console and click outside somewhere.
And we can see the events objects being locked out here.
So that seems to be working.
But we don't want to just log out the event object.
So I'm going to select all of that and add Kelly Braces and add a new line in the middle.
This show Mobile now determines whether or not the mobile menu is shown.
So we can just set this back to false once we've clicked outside.
So in this one click outside method, we can just do show mobile.
Now the value equals false and I'll just remove the event object from here because I'm not going to
need that saved up.
And let's see if it's working.
Show the menu.
Click outside and we see it disappears.
However, it's now not closing the mobile menu and we click on the X, so let's see if we can fix that.
Let's jump up to that button, which is here.
So I think I see what's happening here.
So our mobile menu is currently showing when we click on the burger button.
Well, because this is outside of.
Our mobile menu is triggering the on click outside event on settings show mobile now.
Back to false and hiding the mobile menu.
But because we also have this.
Click on the burger button.
This is then firing this code which is going to show mobile now to the opposite of itself.
So at this point, it's going to set it back to true.
And if we jump back to the on click outside documentation and scroll down a bit, we can actually add
an options object as a third parameter.
After the target and the handler where we can up this ignore option to tell the composable which elements
to ignore the on click outside functionality.
So we can just make it ignore all clicks on this not pop burger.
Now we need to set up a template ref first for this.
Now Bob Burger.
So let's add a ref to this.
Set that to nav bar burger ref.
Save that.
So down.
Now we need to set up our data ref for that hit.
So I'll duplicate this one.
Change this to contact number burger ref.
And then in this one, click outside.
Function.
After our handler function, we can add a comma and then an object.
And that inside that we cannot ignore option set that equal to an array of pass in the template ref.
Solve any elements we want this composable to ignore.
So let's pass in this.
Now popsugar paste that in there.
Save that.
Let's see if that's fixed.
Click on the button on yet.
We can still close it by clicking on the x.
Let's see if we can still click outside to close it.
And yes, we can.