Okay.
So I notes pages looking pretty.
Gosh darn beautiful.
Now let's get this up to actually work by adding some data and methods.
We're also going to turn this note into a child component.
We're going to add a computed property for displaying the number of characters in each note.
And we're also going to set up a custom event using limit.
Well, first of all, let's set up a ref where we can store a list of notes.
So in view notes that view on a scroll down to the bottom, another script sets up tags.
I'm going to create a block comment here which says notes.
We'll set up a constant called notes set that equal to a ref.
We need to import this method.
So a lot another block comment here which says imports and again these comments are optional.
You don't need to add them if you don't want to.
So we need to import ref from view.
And now let's settle our notes.
All right.
So we'll pass an array into this ref on each item.
In the array will be an object, a large, an ID field.
Just set up to ID one.
I'm a lot of content field for the note content.
I'll just stick some lorem in there for some reason.
It's not working right now.
I'll just copy this lorem from a hard hardcoded notes.
Paste that in there and a lot of comma after this object.
Duplicate the note.
Get rid of this comma.
Set the ID to it to.
I'll just change the text on this one.
This is a shorter note.
We'll save that.
Now let's display these notes on our page using a V for directive.
And we already have a V for directive on this day with the class of card which we're using for our notes.
So I'll just change this to be for notes in notes.
So we'll use notes as our place holder as we loop through this notes.
All right.
True.
Set up here.
We also need to add a key property.
I will set this to note it so that this key is always unique.
And I'll save that.
And we can now see two notes on our page.
And we just need to output our content, which is going to be out notes, dark content.
So I'll select this text here in this tape with a class of content at double click basis and then note
the content.
Save that reload.
We can now see our two notes on the page which are now coming from our notes array.