Let's set up an odd note method which gets fired after we type something in this text area and click
the button.
Which then adds this new note to our notes array, thus displaying it on the page.
First of all, that sets up a ref, which we can bind to this text area so that we can actually get
access to the content that the user has typed.
So above our notes.
All right, I'm going to set up a new concept called New Notes Set that equal to a ref with a default
value of an empty string.
And now let's find this constant to our text area.
So we'll scroll up to the text area, which is here out of the model directive, set that to new notes
and save that.
And now if we type something into this ref value here, save that.
We can now see it in the text area.
So let's set that back to an empty string and save that.
Now let's set up a method which is fired when we click on this button.
So I'll jump up to the add new note button, which is here.
I'll split the attributes on the opening tacked on a click click and we'll fire a method called Add
Notes.
And now we need to create this method.
So we'll scroll down after our notes.
All right, we'll set up this method.
Const add notes equals an arrow function.
And for now, I'll just log out, add notes and save that.
Open up the console, click on this button and we can see this method is being fired because we can
see this log being fired.
Now, we don't want the user to be able to click this button if the text area is empty because then
they'd just be adding an empty note.
So let's disable this button when there's nothing in this text area.
So let's jump up to this button.
Which is here.
We can just bind to the disabled attribute and conditionally add this disabled attribute to the bottom.
And we only want to add this attribute.
If this new note ref is an empty string.
So to do that we can just do not.
New note because if that string is empty, it will count as a zero value or a false value.
So let's save that.
We can now see this button is disabled, we can't click it, and if we type something, we can now click
it.
Okay, now let's work on a note method.
So, first of all, we need to set up an object.
With an I.D. and a content property with the content property set to the content that's in the text
area and then push the object to this notes array and we should then see the notes on the page.
So first let's set up this object.
So I'll create a variable called note and set that to an object.
I'm going to need an ID property and a concept property.
Now the concept of property we can just grab from this new note ref, which is bound to the text area
so we can just set this content property to new note dot value.
Now for the ID we need something unique and if you like you could use a package for generating a unique
ID.
So it shows you id i'll just google you id and PM.
And I usually use this, you idiot version full package.
You can use that if you like.
But just for simplicity, I'm just going to use the timestamp in milliseconds from the current date
to generate this ID.
So above this object.
First going to grab the correct timestamp.
So we can just do new date parentheses.
And this will grab the current date as a date object and then to convert that into a timestamp in milliseconds
we can just add dot gets time parentheses and now I'm going to assign this to a variable so it can just
do let's current date equals.
Now this will actually return an integer.
So I'm going to convert it into a string because we're using strings here.
So sets that's another variable called I date I'll set that equal to current date dot to string to convert
that number into a string.
And if we want to shorthand this a bit, we can get rid of the word lat and indent that a bit and just
add a comma after the first variable.
We can now just set this ID property to this ID variable we set up here like that.
Or as a shorthand, since these names are both the same, we can just set this to ID like that.
And now let's just log out this note and make sure this is working.
So console log note, save that.
Let's add some text here.
Click on the button and we can see this object being locked out.
And yeah, we can see the content property and I can see the ID as well, which has been generated.
Based on the timestamp of the current date.
So now all we need to do is push this object to our notes right here.
And we should see the new note on the page.
So to get access to this notes draft, we can just do notes dot value.
So we can just do notes top value.
And then to push this object to the array, we can just do that push and then note.
Now let's save that and see if that's working.
I'll type in a new note.
Click the button, and yet we can see the note added to the page.
And actually it makes sense for our latest note to be at the top of the list.
So instead of pushing get will on shift it, which will basically just stick it at the start of the
array instead of the end of the array.
So I'll just change the word push to on.
Lowercase on shift.
Save that.
Let's try that again.
And yet that's working.
Now it's adding it to the top.
Now, after we add the note, we can see that the text area still has the same content in it that we
just added as a notes.
So let's clear out this text area after we add the new note by just simply setting this new note ref,
which is bound to the text area back to an empty string.
So we can just do new notes.
Value equals empty string.
Let's see if that's working.
Click on the button.
And yet you can see the text area is empty.
We could also use a template ref to refocus this text area after we have the new note as well so that
the user can easily add another note straight away without having to click into this text area.
So let's jump up to the text area elements which is here a lot of ref.
I'll set that to new note ref.
We can now use this ref to focus this text area after we got the new note.
So let's jump back to our aid notes method.
At the bottom here.
We can just do new notes ref dot value to grab the actual text area element and then we can just do
dot focus.
And this should hopefully focus the text area after we have the new note.
So let's save that and reload.
Make sure that's work in.
Hello.
Out of new notes.
This hasn't worked.
New note ref is not defined.
Let's just scroll up and check the ref that we added.
You know, ref.
We need to actually set up a date to rest before we can use this template.
Ref So after this new note counts, let's add another const so that two new notes ref on set that equal
to arrests with an initial value of naught.
Save that and let's reload again.
Hello there.
Click on the button.
And that seems to have worked.
Now we've added the new notes.
We've cleared out the text area and we focus the text area.