This View Notes component is getting quite long now and we're going to be adding some more functionality
to each individual now, such as displaying the number of characters displaying a modal when the delete
button is clicked and sending the user to the edit page when the edit button is clicked.
So before this view notes component gets too messy, let's create a child component for an individual
note.
So I'm going to jump to the Explorer and go to source components.
Let's create a new folder here for all of the components related to our notes.
So we'll call this notes.
And inside that I'll create a new file called Notes dot view.
A lot template tags.
And I'll jump back to view.
Notes that view.
Alma, select all of this, Deb, with the class of card.
Which is displaying a note.
Just copy that.
Paste it into the template tags, fix the indentation and I'll just remove the v4 and the key attributes.
Save that.
Now let's jump back to view notes dot view and import this component.
So in our import section, we'll do import notes from slash components, slash notes, slash note,
dot view.
Save that.
Now, let's scroll up to this, Deb, with the class of card where we're displaying the note above that
we'll use our note component instead.
So note on if we can make this a self-closing tag.
I'll move the closing tag on to a new line.
And now we can just copy the VFR directive on the K property.
Paste it into this note component.
And now we can just get rid of this div or the class of card completely.
And save that reload.
We see an error here.
Cannot read properties of undefined reading content and our app is broken.
And that's because in note dot view in our template, we're trying to access this note object and this
content property from that object.
But this note object doesn't exist within the context of this note dot view component.
So we need to pass this down from view note stop view down to note w using a prop.