Let's pass down the notes object.
Which we're using as the placeholder in our V for loop here down from view notes that view down to note
dot view so that no dot view has access to note dot content.
So don't you know component here.
A lot of call notes and set that equal to note on say that.
And now if we talk to note dot view we need to receive that.
So we need to add a script sets up tasks and a lot of block comment which says props.
Now, do you remember how we initialize our props?
That's right.
We create a constant called props, and we set that equal to define props.
We can pass our props in here either as an array or an object.
I'm going to use an object here.
And so we're going to receive a prop called note, and the type is going to be an object.
And we definitely need this prop in order for our component to render correctly.
So we should also add required through to make this a required prop.
Save that and hopefully this should be working now.
I'll reload and yeah, everything's working again.
We can see our correct note content coming from the parent component array here.
Let's just make sure we can still add a new note.
Yeah.
We can still out a new note.