Let's add a computed property which displays the number of characters that are in each note underneath
the content of the note.
First, let's set up the mock up.
So in note view, underneath where we're spitting out the content, we're going to add a depth and then
inside that, going to add a small tag.
And for now, I'll just put the Tex x x x characters so that we can see that on the page.
To move this text over to the right, I'm going to add a class to the depth of has dashed text dash
right on to give the text a light gray color.
I'm going to add a class of has text dash grey dash lights save that on these classes a from bulma on
there documented on that website.
And just to add a bit of margin, it's a lot of class of empty for margin top dash to save that now
we don't actually need a computed property to display the number of characters we could just do double
kelley braces and then notes, dot content, dot length save that we can see that works.
However, I want to use a computer property somewhere in Iraq just to remind us how we set these up.
So let's remove note that content dot length and instead will create a computer property called character
length, which displays the number of characters of the notes here.
So let's scroll down and set up this computed property called Character Select.
Now do you remember how to do this?
If you like, you can pause the video and see if you can up this on your own.
Did you manage it?
If not, don't worry.
So to add a computed property, first of all, we need to import the computed method from view so allowed
imports comment and we'll import computed from view.
And I'll just see the bottom out.
Another block comment which says character length almost sets a computer property here and we want to
call this character length.
So we'll create a constant called character length.
We'll set that equal to the computed method, and then we'll pass another method into this method.
And now all we need to do in here is return something, and we want to return the length of the concept
property which is in this note prop that we're passing down from view notes dot view.
I remember when we're in a.
Script section.
To access a prop, we do need to use this props object.
So to access this note prop, we can just do prop start notes.
And then to access the content property.
Within that we can just do dark content.
We want to crop the length of that.
We want to return this so we can just add return to the start.
Save that reload.
This seems to be working.
However, one thing you might notice is if we create a note that just has one character.
Then it still says one character's.
It'd be better if it said one character.
So we can adapt a computer property to spit out this word as well based on the number of characters.
So I'm going to jump to our computed property before I do that.
But at your pop to a template, remove the word characters here and we now only see the number.
So let's scroll back down, back to our computed property.
And before we return the value, I'm going to set up a variable called description and we're going to
set this to either character or characters, depending on the length of the note.
And we can use a ternary if statement to do this so we can do let description equals if props dot.
Note the content length is greater than one, then we can use the word characters.
Otherwise we'll use the word character.
And now we can just append this description variable either characters or character to the length that
we're outputting here.
So I'm going to return a template string here.
Place, this prop starting.
Okay, content length and curly braces like that.
And then a lot of space.
And then a lot.
Our description.
So dollar curly braces and then description.
Save that and that's now work.
And you can say 199 characters on one character on the note, which only has one character.
Now we're duplicating a little bit of code here.
Props, dot note, dot content, dot length.
So we could tidy this up a bit by putting it in a variable.
So at the top here I'll add let's, let's call it length equals prop start notes, dot content, dot
length and that I'll replace prop start note not content length both here and here.
I'll press command date to select both of those.
The shortcut might be different on your platform and just replace that with this variable length and
save that.
Make sure it's still working.
Yeah.
We see characters if there's more than one character.
And character.
If there's only one character.