Let's allow a note to be deleted when this delete button is clicked.
And now that this note is in a child component knocked up, you will need to omit an event from note,
not view.
When the button is clicked, then listen out for that event on view notes dot view and then fire another
method here which then removes the note from the notes array.
Since our notes arrays in this parent component are not in this child component.
So first let's just trigger a local method in note dot view when this delete button is clicked.
So let's find the delete button in the template and that's here and I'll split the attributes on that.
A lot of click come to that and I'll also use the Prevent Modifier to stop this link from behaving like
a link and trying to send us to a different page and will trigger a local method called Handle.
Delete Collect.
And let's create this method.
So I'll add another block comment here.
Handle deletes clicked.
I will set up this method.
So const handle delete clicks equals an arrow function.
For now, I'll just log out.
Handle.
Delete.
Clicked.
Save that.
Click on a delete button and you can see that method is being fired.
So now we can emit a custom event from this method.
Well, first of all, we need to set up our emits array.
Do you remember how we do that?
It's a little bit like how we set up props.
And if you want to try it on your own, then feel free to pause the video.
But anyway, I'm going to add a comment which says emits.
And to set up our emits, we can create a constant called emit, set it equal to the define emits method.
And we can pass all of our emits in here in an array.
So let's define and emit called delete.
Clicked on save that and we can now emit this event from this component.
So back to our handle delete click method.
We can now just do emit parentheses and then delete clicked.
Save that, make sure we have no errors.
Now we can listen out for this delete clicked event in the parent component view notes dot view.
So let's jump to that component.
And jump to our notes component here.
I'm a lot.
A custom event under here.
So at Delete Clicks, which is the name we used for our remit when we received that event, let's trigger
a method in this component, so we'll trigger a method called delete note.
Let's create that method.
So down at the bottom, a lot of block comment which says delete notes.
Now we can set up this method const delete notes equals arrow function let's logout delete note for
now save that click on the delete button and yeah we can see this method in the parent component is
being fired.
However, at this point, how do we know which note to remove from the array?
We need something to identify the note that we want to delete so we could use the ID property.
So if we jump back to note dot view, we could pass the note ID along with this omit so we can just
not a second parameter here.
We can grab the ID from this note which we're passing down.
So this is going to be our props.
Don't note Dot's ID.
So in here we can just do props notes.
I'd say that.
Now, let's jump back to the parent component view notes dot view down to this delete note method and
we could pass this parameter in here.
So let's call it ID to delete.
Let's just log that out, make sure it's getting through.
So I need to delete.
Save that.
I'll reload.
Click on a delete button.
Yeah, we can see delete note ID one, which is the idea of the first note.
And if we click on the delete button on the second note, we can see delete note ID too.
So we know that this ID is going through correctly and now there's a number of ways we could remove
the notes from the array.
We could figure out the index of the notes based on the ID and then delete the item, which is index.
But if you want to use a one line solution and we can use filter to set this notes array to itself,
but filtered so that only the notes which don't have this ID are returned.
So what we can do here, we're going to overwrite this notes array ref.
So to access that ref we can do notes dot value and then to overwrite it we can just do equals and we're
going to do notes that value again, but this time we're going to filter it.
So don't filter our first.
We need to add a placeholder which will be used as we're looping through the array, as it's looking
at each item in the array.
So we can just use note for that that we can add an arrow function.
Which will be fired for each note in the array as we're looping through it.
And then we can just specify what we want to return.
I'll just stretch this out a minute.
So let's return only items in the right notes.
The ID is not equal to this idea that we're passing into this function.
So not equal to ID to delete.
And I think they should do it.
So let's save the reload.
Click on Delete.
We can now delete our notes.