I think now's a good time to add state management to our app using peneha on generally speaking.
If you're going to add state management to your app, the earlier the better because adding state management
to an app which is already really complicated, can bring a lot of headaches.
But this time we're going to install Peneha from scratch and set it all from scratch because we didn't
choose to add it to our project automatically.
So let's just Google Kenya.
On July two, the penny a website.
I get started and I'm going to jump to getting started.
So first of all, we need to install it.
With AMPM, our yard.
I'm going to use AMPM, so we need to jump to our terminal.
Kill the deaf process with control see and run ampm install pioneer.
That's installed.
So let's launch our app again with NPM run dev.
Just close the terminal.
And the next thing we need to do is create a PTA, the root store, and pass it to the app.
So we do this in May not.
J.S. So I'll open up the Explorer and go to Source and Main.
Yes.
So first we need to import create Petya from Penta.
So I'll copy this line and I'll paste it after this import create up from view line.
I start in there and now we just need to trigger the use method on our app and then trigger this create
any method within that.
So after this create outline, I'm just going to add don't use parentheses.
And then within that I'm just going to put create a parentheses.
Let's save that.
Make sure we don't have any errors.
So reload the app now.
There's no errors.
So now we need to create a penny store.
I'm going to jump back to the penny side and I'm going to jump backwards to what is Penny A?
On July two.
Basic example, and it gives us a basic example here, and you can put your pennies store files wherever
you want to.
Well, they seem to recommend putting them in this stores folder.
So let's create a new folder in the source folder called Stores and we'll create our still filed here.
And you can call this whatever you like.
I'm going to call it store notes, because this is a store for our notes and all related methods to
those notes.
And I'm just going to copy code of this basic example.
Paste that in here.
So all this is basically doing is using this define stall method to set up our store and we put all
of our state actions and guesses in here.
And then we're just assigning that store to this constant and exporting it to make it available to any
components in our app.
So let's give this constant name a more meaningful name.
So we could call this use store notes.
And also let's get this name here, a more meaningful name.
We could call this store notes.
For now, let's remove this actions object on these two comments and we'll just focus on the state.
To begin with, let's put this onto multiple lines.
And now we can copy our notes right into.
The state in this store so close may not jazz and I'm jump to view notes top view where we currently
have our notes array here.
I'm just going to copy the two objects inside this array for now.
Copy those.
Jump back to store notes.
Such as?
We'll set up a property called Notes.
Set that equal to an array and we'll just paste those notes.
Into this notes array.
Save that.
And we should now be able to import this store into any of our components where they can get access
to this notes array, which is in our state in this store.
Remember, the state is only for storing data.