Let's import this pioneer store we've created into View Notes Dot View Notes Page and use the notes
array that's in our store to display our notes on the page instead of using the notes array, which
we've hardcoded into view notes dot view.
So first of all, we need to import our store into view notes that view.
We want to import this constant here, use store notes.
So let's jump to view notes that view and look to our imports and we'll just add import curly braces.
Use store notes from at slush stores.
Slash store notes.
Say that.
Reload and to get access to the store.
In our component, we need to assign it to a constant or variable.
So a lot another block comment here which says store
and will create a constant called store notes.
On a sign that to use store notes, parentheses, save that.
And now that we've done that, we should be able to see our store in our view.
DevTools So let's click on this little double arrow and then view and it says in the console store note
store installed and we can see our store there.
We click on that.
We can see our notes are array.
And all of the data from each note.
Now let's output these notes from the notes array that's in our store instead of from the array that's
hardcoded into few notes that view here.
So we can just jot two notes component on instead of V for notes in notes.
We can do V for notes in then the name of our store, which is store notes.
So we can do store notes.
And from that store, we want to access the notes.
Right?
So we can just do notes on save that reload.
We can still see our notes on the page, except now they're coming from our store instead of this array,
which is, in our view, notes W component.
So we should now be able to just get rid of this notes array and save that.
We can still see notes on the page.
And if we go to the DevTools.
And we changed the content in one of our notes.
Now we can see our notes all day in real time on the template as well.
I'll just reload that.
And if we jump to store notes, don't just change the content of one of these notes.
I'll just remove some of the text and save it.
And I mentioned earlier on that hot reloading doesn't seem to be working at the moment.
We didn't see the hot reload when I changed the content of this note in the store.
And I also showed you that there's a guide on the PDA site if we scroll down here.
Module replacement.
We attempted to get this work in based on this example, and it wouldn't work.
And I still haven't managed to find a way to get this work in at the time I'm recording this, but feel
free to give it a try.
Maybe it's working now in the future where you are, and if you do find a solution, please share it
with this lecture.
And if I find a solution and a lot of lectures to this course explaining that.