Let's add an action to our A store which will allow us to add a new note to this notes array which is
in our state in our penny store, thus adding the new note to the page.
Since these notes allow coming from these notes right in our state.
Now, if we try to add a new notes right now, we see an error.
Notes is not defined.
That's because if we go to view notes dot view on this add note method on this line here, we're trying
to add a new notes object to this notes array ref which no longer exists here, but we now want to add
a new note object to this notes array which is in our opinion store.
So let's jump back to the penny site and jump to what is Penny a basic example and it shows us here
how we add actions to our store.
So we just need to add an object named actions after our state and we can place all of our actions in
here.
I remember actions are just methods which allow us to access the data in our state and then modify it.
So let's jump back to store notes and for now I'll just collapse the state method and object by just
clicking this little arrow, and after this will add an object called actions and we can now place all
of our actions in here.
So let's create a new option called add note.
And for now, I'm just going to log out a note and say that we can now trigger this action from anywhere
within our app.
So let's trigger it from view, notes dot view.
And we could just trigger this action directly on our Add new notes button here in this clip.
And we're pulling in our store as store notes.
So to access our store, we could just add store notes and then to access the action, we've just added
notes.
We can just add dots, add notes, and we don't need to add parentheses to this method when we're triggering
it in our template.
So let's save that and see if that's working.
I'll type in a note and click add new notes and yeah, we can see a note being locked out.
So this is successfully firing our action.
However, if we jump down to our previous ADD note method which is on view notes dot view, we have
these two lines at the bottom.
This one which is clearing out the new notes, ref those clearing the text area and this line which
is focusing the text area by using this template ref that we've set up which we've added to the text
area here.
Now we're not going to have access to this remodel to clear out all this template ref to focus the text
area from within our store so it makes sense to continue to trigger this local method.
Add note when we click on the odd new note button and then trigger our action from here so that we can
still fire these two lines at the bottom, which are going to clear out the text area and focus the
text area.
So let's change that.
Click on the add new note button back to what it was triggering this local Add Notes method and we'll
comments how all of this code which was setting up the new note object and then on shifting it to notes
array ref which we had here before and then will trigger the action in our store instead.
So we can just do store notes, dot odd notes, and when we're triggering an action from our script
section, we do need to add parentheses.
So let's save that and see if that action in our store is still being triggered.
I'll reload, type in a note and click the button and yet we can see a note being displayed.
Well, this action needs to know what we should actually add to our notes right in the state.
So we need to actually pass the content of this note which has been typed into the text area to this
option.
So we can set up a new note object based on this content and then add it to our notes array that's in
the state.
We could do this using parameters.