We need to pass the new notes content from view notes dot view to our new add notes action which is
in our store.
Before we can set up a new note object and add it to this notes array that's in our state, we can pass
parameters to actions as many parameters as we like, just like we can with any function in JavaScript.
So let's jump back to view notes that view and our new note content is in this new note ref which is
bound to this text area.
So when we trigger our action here, we can just do store notes to add notes and then pass in new notes
value and save that.
Now if we jump back to our store notes on this note action, we can receive this parameter here and
we can give it any name we want.
So we could call it new notes content.
To make sure this is getting through.
Let's just log it out here.
So new notes, content.
Save that reload, click the button and yeah, that's work.
And we can see our action is logging out the note that we just typed.
So now we just need to set up a new notes object like this with an ID and a content property and then
add it to this notes right in our state.
So let's jump back to view notes dot view.
Unless this code that we commented out say that I will paste that into our action here.
Remove the comments, fix the indentation.
We're going to need to modify this a bit.
So this line is still fine.
That's still going to get the current date on this line is fine.
It's just going to convert that timestamp into a string and assign it to this ID variable.
Then we up a new notes object and we're already setting up our ID, so that's fine.
But when we set the content property, we no longer want to grab this from new notes value.
We want to grab it from this parameter that we're passing in new notes content.
So let's copy that and paste that here.
And then when we shift this new notes object to our notes array.
We now want to push it to this notes array that's in our state, and we can access the data properties
in our state inside an action using the this keyword a bit like we did in the options API.
So to access our notes array, which is just called notes, we can just do this.
The notes that we want to on shift this notes objects into this array so we can just do this start notes,
start on shift parentheses around notes, and we can now just get rid of this line.
Now let's save that and see if this is working.
Type in a new note.
Click the button on yeah, it's work and we see it added to the page.
In depth tools we can see it's been added to our notes.
A right in our state here as well.