Let's set up an action in our opinion store for deleting a note and our delete button is in a note component
and components notes a note dot view.
So let's see what's happening right now with this delete functionality.
So on this delete button here we have this click handler which is going to fire this local method handle
delete clicked.
And that method is here.
And then inside that we're emitting a custom event called Daily Clicked on passing in the ID of the
notes that we want to delete.
Then in the parent component, view notes that view to scroll up to the notes component.
We're listening out for this custom event when we receive it with triggering this delete note method.
And with that removing the note from the array based on this ID that we're passing it and this local
notes.
Right.
No longer exists here.
So this is not going to work anyway at the moment.
But anyway, once we start using state management in our app, whether it's through composable view
or any other like we're using, we don't need to worry about imitating custom events from child components
to parent components, and then listening out for those events before we trigger a method.
Because remember, all of the components of our app, no matter how deeply nested they are, have access
to everything that's in store, including everything in our state and all of our actions.
So let's set up a new delete note action in our store and trigger it directly in note dot view without
needing to emit any custom events or listen out for those events.
Okay, so let's jump to store notes.
And I'll just collapse this add note action at a comma and add a new action called delete notes in order
to delete the note from notes.
Right.
In our state, we're going to need the ID date.
So we'll set this up to receive the ID eight with a variable called ID to delete.
I will just log out id to delete as well.
I need to delete and save that.
Now back in note dot view.
Instead of triggering this local method handle delete clicked when this delete button is clicked.
Let's import our opinion store here and trigger this new action delete note directly instead.
So I'm going to jump to view notes.
Start view copy this line where we're importing store, paste that at the top of note dot view that
we need to get access to our store like we did on the stock view by assigning our store to a constant.
So I'm going to copy this comment on the code as well from view notes dot view and we'll paste that
after our props on limits and we now have access to our store in this note dot view component.
So we can now jump to this delete button, trigger this delete note action directly.
So we'll get rid of this handled really clicked message call and instead we'll just do store notes,
dot delete note.
Now we need to pass in the note ID and remember we're passing down the notes object with a prop here.
So our note ID is available.
Props notes ID or just notes ID if we're in the template so we can just pass in notes the ID save that
and hopefully our action delete note should be receiving the ID and logging its out.
So let's see if that's working.
Click on the delete button.
When we see ID one being locked out, click on the other delete button and we see ID to be and logged
out.
Now let's jump back to note dot view and do some tidying up because we no longer need this handled delete
click method.
We're not using it anymore and we also no longer need to define delete clicked as an omits because we're
no longer omitting that.
So we can just remove our omits code and the comment entirely, save that.
And if we want to view notes that view, scroll up to the note component.
We no longer need to listen out for this DeLay Clicks event.
We're no longer emitting it from note dot view, so we can remove that as well, save that and if we
scroll down here, we're now no longer firing this delete note method.
So I'm just going to copy the code from inside this method and then just delete this method on the comment
as well.
Save that.
Now let's jump to store notes as I will paste this code into this delete note method.
We just need to adjust this a little bit.
So we're no longer going to filter notes to value and then assign that filter to write back to notes
the value.
We now want to do that with this notes array that's in our state.
So again, we can just replace this notes dot value or select both of these by holding now alt.
Instead we can just do this dot notes.
So this is going to grab the entire notes array and filter it based on the criteria in here.
And it's going to return all of the notes where the note ID is not equal to the ID that we're passing
in here and these variable names are still the same.
So I don't think we need to make any more changes.
So let's save that and we'll see if this is working.
So I'll reload, click on a delete button and we can see the note is deleted.
And we also see that object removed in our Def tools as well.
And if I delete this one, we now see an empty right in our def tools.