So we can now create, read and delete notes, but we can't currently update a notes.
So that's complete crud set up create read update delete by creating a new edit note page which will
allow us to edit a note and save it.
For this, we're going to be adding a new action to any store and also our first getter.
But for now, let's just set up a new route page for editing a note.
So when it jump to our Explorer and in the Views folder, I'm going to create a new file called View.
Edit Note.
Don't view a lot of template tags to begin with.
I'm just going to get a diff with a class of edit dash notes and inside that a lot of hate one tag which
just says edit notes on save that.
And now we need to set up our route.
So let's jump to source router and index dot jess.
A lot of new route here after the few notes route when to select all that and press alt shift and dow
shortcut might be different for you to duplicate that.
I will set the path to edit notes in order to follow this route to know which notes that we're going
to actually edit load into the page.
Then we're going to need to pass a routes parameter to this path.
So to do that, we can just add slush and then colon and then the name of a parameter and we could just
call it ID.
So in other words, we could visit the edit, note slash ID one and then we can grab that ID I'd want
on this view and then use it to grab the appropriate notes.
In our notes are right in our state, in our store, and then display the contents of this notes in
a text area on this page so that we can then edit it and save it.
Let's change the name of this route.
To edit Dash notes, we need to import our new component so we'll duplicate this import view notes line
and replace view notes with view edit notes and then I'll copy this name view edit now paste it in here
so I'll save that.
We should now be able to visit parts such as edit notes, slash ID one and get to our new edit note
page.
Okay, now we need to be able to get to this page without having to type in the address bar.
So let's hook up these edit buttons.
I'm just going to close everything here except note dot view and let's find our edit button and that's
here.
I'm going to break this up onto new lines and then split the attributes on the opening text.
And we can actually just change this into a routes of view component.
Instead of an attack.
So let's rename the tag to root a link.
Make sure the closing tag is renamed as well, and we can now just add a two to this to tell it where
to go.
So I'm going to use a template string to do this using tactics so that we can output the ID and we want
to go to the path slash edit note which we set up in our route to file and then slash and then we'll
use dollar curly braces to output the ID on again.
We're passing the note objects down to this note dot view component using this notes so we can get access
to the ID, props notes, the ID or in the template.
Just note the ID.
So in here we can just put notes Dot's ID and let's save that.
See if these edit buttons are working.
Click on the first edit button on yet the path edit note slash.
I'd want to jump back click on the second edit button and we're now on the path edit note slash ID too.
We can access this root parameter which we've named ID in our route to file here in our template by
using the dollar route object, which we could also use the options API.
So let's just spit out this route parameter ID on the page and see if that's working.
So we want to open up our new view.
Edit Note Component.
So source views view edit note and let's change this.
Heading to edit notes with on ID of and then we'll do double Kelly braces and to access our routes information
we cannot route and then to access our routes parameters we can do doc params and then to access our
ID parameter which we set up here, we can just do dot IP.
So hopefully this will be spitting out our notes ID on the page now.
So let's save that reload and yeah, if we're at the path edit note slash I'd say we see ID two on the
page and if we click on the first edit button and we go to the path edit note slash 81, we now see
ID one on the page.