Okay.
So what are we actually going to need on this new edit note view that we've created in order to edit
a note and save it?
Well, basically what we need is a text area which we can load the note into and allow the user to edit
it.
And we need a save button so the user can save it.
So basically what we need is if we go back exactly what we have at the top of our notes view here,
we just need a text area and a button.
Now we could just jump to our notes, view and source views, view notes, and we could just copy this
card element and all of the fields inside it.
Paste that into view, edit no view and then repurpose it.
Well then we'll be duplicating code and we always want to avoid duplicating code as much as possible
so it makes more sense to create a reusable component out of this card.
The text area on the bottom that we can use anywhere within our app.
So let's jump to our Explorer in our notes folder.
Let's create a new file called Add edit note dot view because we are going to be able to see both ADD
and added to note using this component.
Let's add template tags.
Now let's jump to view notes dot view and we'll copy this markup.
So this did with the class of card and all the stuff inside it will copy that.
Paste it into our template here in our new component.
Now let's remove all of the dynamic stuff which will break here.
So let's remove this view model from the text area and remove this.
Click on the disabled prop from the well to save that.
Now we want to be able to control the buttons that get displayed here because on our notes page we want
this new note button, but on the edit page, then we probably want a button that says save or save
note or something like that.
And we might also want to be able to add more than one button as well.
So let's create a slot here where we can insert any button that we want.
So I'm just going to get rid of this button and instead will add a slot and we'll make this a named
slot.
So a lot of name attribute and set that two buttons, save that.
Now let's use this new component on our notes view and get it all working that before we then use it
on our new edit page.
So let's jump to view notes dot view and we'll import this component that we just created that after
our notes import.
So I'll duplicate this line and we're going to import add edit note from slash component slash notes
slash edit notes that view.
Save that.
Now let's scroll up.
I will comments how all of this card element.
And then outputs are a new component.
Add edit notes save the.
We see the text area, but we don't see the button.
We need to press the button into a slot.
So inside this odd edit note component, we can add a template tag and we can either at the dash slot
colon buttons, which is the name of the slot that we set up on.
Edit Note View here.
Or we can shorthand this by just doing hash buttons.
We can now place outputs and it here.
So let's grab that from the markup that we come and sit out.
So the button is here, so I'll copy that, paste it in here and save that.
Everything looks correctly now, but it's not working because this text area, which is now coming from
our new reusable component, is no longer hooked up to this new note ref in our script section.
So let's fix that next.