This text area on the button are no longer working.
And that's because this text area, which is in our new child component add edit note that view is no
longer hooked up to this new note ref which we set up in this do notes component.
Well, what we can do is pass this new note ref down to add edit note child component using v model.
Then we can hook it all up using model value and update model value.
So first let's set the V model of this add edit note component to new note, which was originally bound
to the text area so we can add a V model directive and set that to new notes.
Save that and we can now receive the value of this V model in a add edit note component using the special
model value and then we can bind that prop to this text area.
Do you remember how we do that?
Feel free to pause the video and give it a try.
So what we need to do is add a script, set up tags, and we need to receive the value of this V model
using the model value prop.
So we need to set up props and we do that by adding a constant called props set by equal to the define
props method.
And we can pass our props in here and we want to receive the model value.
Prop on the type is going to be string.
This is going to be required.
So we'll set required to save that.
We can now bind this model value prop to the text area.
We can do that by just setting the V model to model value and I'll save that to check.
This is working.
Let's jump to a few notes that view.
I will change the default value of this new note ref.
And that's here.
So I'll stick some text in there, save that.
And we can say that text is getting through to the text area in our new reusable component.
However, if we output this new note ref somewhere on our page.
So let's say we had a pretext after this odd edit note component and we just output new notes, save
that reload and then we make a change to the text area.
We can see the value of this new note ref is not being updated and so what we need to do in our new
child component.
Edit Note W is explicitly let the parent component know a few notes that view when the value in the
text area has changed so that it can update the value.
In this new note ref and we can do that using update model value.
So let's jump to add edit note w and you remember how we do that.
Again, feel free to pause and try and do it yourself.
But what we need to do is set up our omits.
So create a constant called emit so the equal to the define emits method and we could pass in our emit
events into this define emits array and we want to add the event update code on model value.
This is a special event which will allow us to directly modify a value that's coming from the parent
component by a V model without having to emit any events from the child component and listen out for
those events and then make the change.
So update model value allows us to modify this new note ref, which is on its parent component.
So let's jump back to add edit note w and what we can do here is listen out for the input event on this
text area which will be triggered every time we make a change to this text area.
So we can just add that input.
And what we want to do is emit with emit and we want to emit the update column model value event.
We need to pass in the value that we want to set up to assign set the value that's being passed down
with the V model on the parent component as the second parameter.
And so we can just set that to model value, save that, let's see if that's working.
Reload this page, change the value of the text area.
And yeah, we can see this pre tag on the view notes dot view component is being updated.
So we know that this new note ref on the parent component is being successfully updated by the child
component add edit note up view by listening out for the input event on the text area and then emitting
the update model value event passing in the latest value which will then directly update the value of
the model you note, which we're passing in here.
So before we move on, let's remove this pre tag that we added on all of this code that we commented
out.
Get rid of that.
And we also need to set the default value of new note up to an empty string.
Save that reload.
Let's make sure everything is working.
So I put a new note, click on the button and the new note was added.
However, we see an error in our console, cannot read properties a note reading focus.
And that's because in this line here, after we add a new note by sending the note content to our add
note action in our store, we're trying to focus an element which has a template ref of new note ref.
And this ref no longer exists on this component.
This template ref is now down in the child component add edit note dot view here.
And so that's why this text area is not focusing after we add a new note and that's why we're seeing
this error.
So let's fix that next.