When we type in a new note, click the add new note Watson.
We can see the notes is added to our list and added to our opinion store.
To the notes are right in the state.
However, the text area is not refocused and we see this error in the console.
Cannot read properties of note reading focus.
And that's because in view notes the view after we update notes to the notes are right in the store.
We're using this template ref, new note ref to grab the text area element and then focus it.
Well, this template ref new note ref no longer exists in this view notes component.
So let's remove this constant here which we set up for the template ref and also remove this line where
we were focusing the text area and find another way to do this.
One thing we could do instead is add a template ref to the add edit note component that we're displaying
here and use that template ref to get access to the child component, add, edit note and then fire
a method that sets it within the edit note few component.
So let's add a riff to this component and we'll call it add edit note ref save.
That will jump down to the bottom.
We need to set a data for this as well with the same name, so create a constant called add edit note
ref set not equal to a data ref with an initial value of note.
And now in a note method here after we clear the new note ref thus clearing the text area, we cannot
access the child component add edit note by using this template ref so we can do that edit notes ref
dot value to access that component and we can then trigger a method which is in that component.
So let's say we want to trigger a method called focus text area.
We can do this like that.
Now, we haven't set up this focus text area method yet, so let's save that.
And to add edit note dot view sets up this method.
So that's not a new section here with a comment which says focus text area and we'll create this method.
So const focus text area equals an arrow function on for now I'll just log out, focus text area and
save that.
So let's see if this method in the child component focus text area is being successfully triggered by
its parent component view.
Note Stop view here.
So let's reload.
And this method should be fired after we add a new note.
So let's type in some text.
Click on the button.
That's not worked and we see this error.
Edit Note ref dot value.
The focus text area is not a function, so it's not able to find this function that we just set up in
the child component.
And that's because when we're using the script setter pattern, we need to actually expose any methods
that we want to be made available to a component's parent component.
And we do this by using the define expose method.
We pass into that an object.
We just want to add in here any methods that we want to be made available to this component's parent
component.
So we want to make this focus text area method available so we can just add focus text area here.
So let's save that and see if that's not working.
Type in a note, hit the button.
Yet that's working.
Now we can say focus text area being locked out so operate component do you stop view is successfully
triggering this focus text area method on its child component to edit note dot view.
So now all we need to do in order to focus this text area is add another template ref to this text area
and then use that to focus it here.
So let's scroll up to the text area element on this text area still has a ref on it from before this
new note ref.
Well, this text area is not just for new notes anymore, it's also going to be used for editing notes.
So let's rename this ref to text area ref, which is a bit more generic and we'll use this ref to focus
the text area.
So let's jump down to our focus text area method.
And we also need to set up a data ref for this template ref with the same name.
So we want to do const text area ref set that equal to a ref with an initial value?
No, let's just check if we're importing the ref method from view and we're not.
So let's just add an import section at the top and we'll import ref from view.
Don't back down to method.
So now to get access to the text area element, we can just do text area ref dot value and then to focus
it, we can just fire the focus method.
So to focus save that and hopefully this should be working now type in a new note hit the button on
yeah it's worked.
We've added the new note.
We can see it on the page and we've also cleared the text area and focused it as well.