Let's add our new reusable component add edit note w to undo edit note page.
So I'm going to jump to view notes where we're currently using the add edit note component and I'll
just copy this, close that jump to the new view view, edit, note, dot view and will paste that inside
this diff.
Let's just remove all of the dynamic content for now.
So I'll remove the V model and remove the click handler on the disabled attribute.
Save that.
We need to import this component before we can use it.
So let's order.
Script sets up tags at our imports section and we'll import and edit notes from slash components.
Slash notes slash at edit notes the view save that we can now see that component on the page.
I was seeing a warning in the console here missing required prop model value and that's because this
component to edit note dot view is expecting the model value prop or the V model prop on this is set
to a required prop.
So let's set up a ref on view edit note dot view that we can bind to this add edit note component.
So in our script section, a lot of new content which says note will sets up a ref called note content
so that equal to a ref with an initial value of an empty string.
Because we're using the ref method, we need to import this.
So let's import ref from view and now we can bind this ref to our add edit note component so it cannot
be model on.
Remember, all we need to do is not the V model because we've already set up this add edit note component
to automatically pull in whatever v model we pass into this component using the model value prop and
automatically update the V model which is on the parent component by using the update model value event.
So all we need to do now is just bind this no content ref to this component.
So we'll set this V model to note content on save that.
Let's just make sure that's hooking up.
I'll put some text in here and yeah, we can see the update on the text area.
So let's set that back to an anti string and save that.
Let's change the text on this button here.
So we'll change this text to save note, save up.
Now I would like this card which is surrounding our text area and bottle to have a different color when
we're on the edit page.
So it looks a little bit different from the card secretariat button, which is on the notes page.
And if we open up our reusable component add edit no doubt view, we can see this class on the card
has background success.
We can change this word success to create different colors.
So for example we can change this to has background link doc to give it this blue collar.
So let's set up a prop on this add edit note the view component so that we can dynamically change this
word here, thus changing the color.
I'll set this back to success for now and save that now let's jump down to props and we'll set up a
new prop called BG Color and we'll set the type to string and we'll get this a default value as well.
So if we don't provide this prop on a parent component, we can still have a background color on this
card.
So we'll set the default to success.
I'll save that.
And now let's jump up to this, Dave, with the class ID card.
I'll split the attributes on that and I'm going to cut this has background success doc plus I will bind
to the class attribute.
I'll use a template string here using optics so that we can output the content of this prop.
I'll paste in that class that we copied as background success.
Doc Let's just get rid of the word success and a dollar Kelly braces an output prop and set BG color
and we can either do props BG color or we can just to BG color, so we'll save that reload.
Now we can see that if we don't provide this BG color prop to this add edit note component, when we
use it on a parent component, then we see the default background color because it's going to use this
default value in the prop which we set here.
But we should be able to override this word success by providing this prop to the add edit note component
when we use an apparent component.
So let's jump to view, edit note dot view a lot this prop to our add edit note component here.
So we'll set BG color.
I will set this to link save up and we now see this blue color and if we inspect it, we can see that
the card house this class has background links.
But if we go to the notes page and inspect card, we can see the class has background success dog.
So that background color is working.
Now let's also make a save notes button, the same kind of color as well.
The save notebook is here, so let's change that class to has background link instead of success.
Save that we now have a blue button.
While we're at it, let's disable this button when this field is empty.
So again, we'll update disabled.
Review conditionally only when no content is empty.
So we'll set this to not note content.
Save that and that button is disabled by default.
But if we type something in, then it becomes enabled again.
Now we also need to make this placeholder text in the text area customizable as well because the text
add a new note doesn't make sense on this page because this text area is going to be for editing a note
and not adding a new note.
So let's add another prop add edit note the view for this placeholder text which is currently just hardcoded
onto the text area.
So we'll set up a new prop called placeholder set to a type of string and we'll give this a default
value of, let's say type something, dot, dot, dot.
Save that.
Now let's use this prop on our text area so we can just bind to the place, hold the attribute, and
then output this prop either with prop stock, placeholder or just placeholder.
So I'll save that reload.
We can now see the default value of type something in the placeholder, but we should not be able to
override this by passing in this place.
Hold a prop to our to edit note component when we use it on one of our pages.
So let's jump to view edit note that view.
I will at this place hold a prop so placeholder we could set this to edit note save that and we see
that in the text area.
If we jump back to our notes, page is still says type something.
So let's override that as well.
So we'll open up view note stock view.
I will love this placeholder prop here as well to our edit note component.
So placeholder.
Almost at least to add new notes.
Say that.
Let we see the update.
I'd also like to be able to display a label at the top of our text area to make the function of this
text area a bit clearer.
So first, let's just set up the markup for this.
So if you want to add edit, note up for you.
And at the top of our card element above this field, I'm going to add a label with a class of label.
For now, I'll remove this fall attribute and I'll just set the text to label text for now.
Save that.
Let's make this white.
So a lot of class of has text white to make it white.
And again, these classes are just from Beaumont, and I want this label to be optional.
So let's set up another prop for this.
So we'll set up a prop called label and set that to a type of string.
Save that.
And I only want to display this label element on the page if this prop has been provided.
So I'm going to split the attributes on this and we can just add a V if directive.
We only want to display this if the label prop has been provided.
So we can either do V if props that label or just V if label.
So I'll save that and we see that label disappear.
Since we're not actually providing this label prop to this add edit note component when we use it on
our edit page here.
But if we add this label prop here, so label because that is to edit notes, save that and reload.
We can now see the label again since we're providing this prop, although it's not displaying the value
that we're passing in here.
So let's jump back to add edit note dot view and we can just output the contents of this prop here so
we can just replace label text with double click prices and label save that and we now see edit note.
And if we jump back to the notes view and we don't see that label since we're not providing that label
prop on the View Notes page here.
And the reason that I think we need a label here is because when the user clicks on edit notes, they're
not going to see an empty text area here.
They're going to see this text area populated with the note, and so they won't see that placeholder.
So this will just give the user a little bit more clarification before we move on and start adding a
new getter to our opinion store for getting the content of the note that the user's trying to edit out
an action for updating the note that's just got a council button here, which takes us back to the notes
page since right now there's no way for the user to get back aside from clicking on the back, put it
so we're jump to view edit note dot view on inside our button slot.
Here, we'll just add another button so I'll duplicate this save note, remove the disabled prop, change
the text to cancel save that out I'm going to change this class house background linked to is dash light
to give it this light gray color.
Now there's a couple of ways that we could send the user back to the notes page when they click on this.
One thing we could do is convert this button into a root to link component, set the two prop to slash,
save that.
See if that works, that works.
The other thing we could do is leave this as a button.
And at a click, how much of this click?
We could use the dollar router method because we can still use the dollar router method in our templates
using the composition API.
So we could either do dollar roots dot push forward slash see if that works.
Yeah, that works.
Or if our app was more complicated and had lots of different ways that we would get to this edit page
from different pages, then we might want to just send the user straight back to wherever they just
came from.
So to do that, we could just do dollar roots, dot back parentheses, save that reload, and that works
as well.