When the user clicks on this edit button, they're taken to this new edit note page and they're going
to expect the text of the note that they just clicked on this text here to be loaded into this text
area.
And we can do this by using a getter in our opinion store.
So what we're going to need to do is grab the ID of the current note from our root parameters, which
we can see in our address bar, hit ID one, and then send that ID to a getter in our store, which
will then retrieve the correct note from our notes array in our store based on that ID and return it
to this view.
Edit Note component where we can then assign it to this note content ref which is bound to the text
area, thus populating the text area with the text from the correct note.
But to begin with, let's just set up a really simple getter which just gets the content of the first
note in our array.
So let's jump to our store file, store notes, stock.
JJ's in the stores folder and we'll scroll down and to add some guesses we just need to add a gets objects
up to this actions object.
We can place all of our guesses in here.
And so to get to that we just had a property with the name of the get to that we want we could call
it get note consent and then we assign this property to a method like this so that this getter can get
access to US state.
We need to pass the state into this.
Gets like this and gets us.
Always need to return something just like computed properties.
So for now, let's just return the content from the first notes in our notes array in our state so we
can grab this from state dot notes and then square brackets zero to grab the first no dot content.
Let's get the content of that first note so it gets up.
All we need to do is return state dot notes, square brackets, zero to grab the first one dot content
and save that.
And we should now be able to use this getter anywhere in our app.
So let's use it on view edit note dot view.
We need to import our store so we need to do import use store notes from slash stores, slash store
notes that we need to assign this to a constant so that we can access it.
So a lot of new comment which says Store, I will set up a constant called store notes set that equal
to use store notes parentheses and actually let's move this up a bit to cut that paste after our imports.
And now we can use the getter in our store to grab that content from the first note on assign it to
this note content ref, which should then update the text area.
So to access our getter we can just do store notes dot and then the name of our getter which is get
notes content.
We just want to assign this to this note content ref so we can just do notes content dot value equals
like that.
So let's save that now reload.
That doesn't seem to be working.
Let's have a look in our console, not seeing any errors.
Let's have a look at a still file.
So make sure the app is running.
Yeah, it's running.
Oh, it help if we were actually on the edit page.
So let's click on an edit bottom.
Yeah, we can see the text from the first notes is being loaded into this text area.
However, we don't just want to grab the text from the first notes.
Right.
We need to be able to grab the content from the notes based on the idea of the note that they just clicked
on.
So if we click on edit on the second note, then we expect to see this notes content being loaded into
here.
So we can grab the ID that's being passed to this page using our root parameters.
And we saw earlier on that we can spit this out in our template using the route object.
So after this add edit notes, I'll just add a pre tag double curly braces and then dollar routes dot
params and then the name of our parameter.
I'd say that.
So we need to pass this ID to get to so that that gets i can get the content follow the correct note.
However, we need to do this in our script section and we can't access our root information in the script
section using the dollar route object.
When we're using the composition API, we need to use view routes as new use routes composable.
So let's just remove this pre tacked on after this import here, we'll import use route from view dash
router and then a lot of comment here which just says route to and we need to assign this user out composable
to constant or variable.
So we'll set up a contact called routes set that equal to use route parentheses.
We can now access the same routes information which we just spat out before using this route constant.
So let's just see if we can log out this route parameter, this ID parameter.
So after we set up this note content rest, we'll just log out.
So consolidate log routes dot params dot i d save that and yet we can see id two is being locked out.
And if we go back to the notes page and click on edit on the first note and we see ID one being locked
out.
So how can we pass the value of this ID to getter?