So how can we pass this ID to get it?
Well, you might think that we could just start parentheses to our get to here and pass it in like this.
Route dot params dot.
I'd say that.
Then just to still file down to get to and maybe pass this parameter in as a second parameter.
Well, we can see this doesn't work.
We see an error in the console store notes don't get no content is not a function.
And that's because this is not a function.
It's just an object property that's assigned to a function.
But we can get around this by making God gets a return a function with the parameter that we're passing
through.
So let's get rid of this ID parameter and get rid of this return line.
What we can do is just return an arrow function like this.
Pass in the parameter here so ID and let's see if we can lock this out now.
So console log on.
A lot of string key I.D. from getter colon and then we'll spits out this ID parameter, so we'll save
that reload.
Now we can see that's working ID from getter ID one and we see a warning here, but don't worry about
that.
That's just because getter is returning a function up moment and not a string.
And we're assigning that to this note content ref which is being passed to add edit note in the v model
on the model value prop on this component is expecting a string.
So we'll see this disappear when we get get to work.
So let's jump back to store notes as and now we can use this I.D. to grab the correct notes on this
content property from the notes array that's in our state so we can use filter to do this.
So inside this method here, we're going to return our notes.
All right, so state the notes, but then we're going to filter it with the filter method, stretch
this out a bit.
So this is going to loop through each item in our array.
So we're going to need a placeholder for each item as it's going through.
So we'll use note for that.
Then we add another arrow function, specify criteria for the notes that we want to grab and we want
to grab the notes where the ID property is equal to the ID property that we're passing in here from
our edit note page.
So we want to return notes where the ID is equal to ID.
And since all of our IDs are going to be unique, that this will return an array containing just the
note object that we're looking for.
So since this is going to be an array, we need to grab the first and only item from the array by adding
square brackets zero.
And then from that we want to drop the content property so we can just do dot content.
Let's save that and see if this is working.
Reload the page.
Okay.
So we're edit notes id and we are seeing the content from the notes with an ID of ID one.
And if we jump back to the notes page, click on edit on the second note, then we see the content from
the second note with ID to being loaded into the text area.