When the user makes a change to this note and they click on Save, we want to update the content property
of the correct note in our state with the new content that they've typed in.
I'm first of all, let's just trigger a local method when we come the save button.
So I'm going to jump to view, edit, note dot view and I'm going to remove this console log here unless
John put it to our save note button.
And I'm also going to add a bit of margin between these buttons actually.
So on the console button a lot and dash three, let's say maybe two and that looks a bit better.
Now let's start a click on let's do this save note button.
So I click equals I will trigger a method called handle save clicked and let's go and create that method.
A lot of new comment here which says save clicked.
Sets about method handle save clicked so they equal to an arrow function on just log out handle save
clicks for now save that click on the button.
We can see that's being locked out.
So we're going to trigger an action in our store at this point to update the notes.
In our notes are right in the state.
So what information is that action going to need in order to do that?
Well, it's going to need the notes ID so that we can figure out which notes in the array to actually
update on.
It's also going to need the new content string as well.
So there's a couple of ways we could pass this information to an action in our store.
So we could set up an object.
We could call it payload or something like that.
We could add a couple of properties today so ID, which we can again get from our root properties.
So root stop, params ID and then a content property which we can just grab from this note content ref
which is bound to the text area.
So notes content value.
And then we could just pass this whole payload as a single parameter to an action.
And in fact, with the UX, this was the only way that we could do this, because actions in view X
can only accept one parameter.
However, actions in Pioneer can actually accept multiple parameters.
So the other way to do this is just to send the ID and the content as two separate parameters.
So in this case, I think we should do it that way because it will make our action a bit more clear,
because we'll be able to see exactly what's being passed in here.
So let's set up this action.
So we'll create a new action called Update Notes, and this is going to receive an ID parameter on a
content parameter.
Now let's just log these out.
So a log out ID and then we'll log out the content parameter as well.
Save that.
And now let's trigger that action here.
And our action is going to be store notes, dot update notes, because this is the name we gave our
action here.
And this is going to expect an ID parameter on the content parameter.
So the ID we're going to grab from our root parameters, root stopped Ram's ID and then the content
we're just going to grab from this no content ref, which is bound to the text area so we can get that
from note content dot value.
Now let's save that and see if these two parameters are getting through to this action.
Reload.
Change the content.
Click on Save and yet we can see those being locked out by our action.
You see the ID being locked out and the updated content being locked out as well.
So now we just need to update the correct notes in our state.
And one way we could do that is by first figuring out the index or the position of the notes in our
array, by using the find index method.
And then we can just simply update the notes in our right at that position and update the content property.
So first of all, let's just grab the index of the notes that we want to update.
So we'll set up a variable called index, and then we're going to fire the find index method on our
notes.
Right.
And we can get to our notes about this stop notes.
So we can do this stock notes, dot find index.
And again, we'll use note as our placeholder as it's looping through our array set that equal to an
arrow function and we want to return the index of the notes where the notes ID is equal to this idea
that we're passing to this action, so equal to it.
And actually, I think we can just shorthand this by removing these curly braces and the word return.
Let's just see if that works.
And also I'll do the same to this filter down here can shorthand this by removing the parentheses return
on this closing parentheses.
Since we're only firing one line here and here.
So let's just log out this index and see if that's working.
Index.
Say that.
Reload the page and change it and click on Save.
Yeah, we can see that index is set to one here, which is correct, because that's a second note.
And I could jump back to the first.
Now make a change and click Save.
Let me see.
Index zero being logged out.
Okay.
So now that we have the index of the notes that we want to update in our notes array, we can now update
the notes.
So let's scroll down to our update.
Note action.
When I get rid of these console dot looks to access our notes array, we can just do this stop notes
and then to access the notes at the position of index, we can just do square brackets index.
Then we want to access the concept property and set it to this content that we're passing through to
this action.
So set that equal to content and remove this console.log and let's see if that's working.
So I'll reload.
Make a change.
New content.
Click on Save.
Now, if we click on Cancel, we can see that the first note has been updated with the new content.
Let's make sure it works on the second note as well.
Click on edit.
Add some new content.
Click on Save.
Click on Cancel.
And this note has been updated as well.
However, when the user does click Save on this button, we don't want to leave them hanging on this
page.
We really want to redirect them back to the notes page.
So let's do that next.
But before we move on, I've just realized there's another return statement here that we can show.
So I'm going to remove this curly brace in our delete note action and return.
I don't remove the closing Kelly Price as well.
Let's have a look at the up note action so that one's okay as it is.
Okay, let's save that.