Let's redirect the user back to the notes view after this note has been saved.
So let's jump to view edit note to view.
So we need to do this in our script section after this line.
So in the options API, we could just do this dot dollar to then not push on, push them to the top.
Well, in the composition API, this is not going to work.
So let's get rid of that.
And we need to import the use router composable from view router.
So let's jump up to the top on here where we're importing use route.
We can just add use router to that.
We need to assign this to a constant before we can use it.
So we can do that after we've set up our use route constant.
So we can just do const use actually const routes equals use router.
And we can now access all of the usual routes of methods such as push and replace and back using this
constant.
So now down to handle save collect method.
After we update the note, we can just do router push and we'll push them back to the notes page which
is up the path slash.
Let's say that and see if that's working.
Reload the page, change the content to save.
And yet we're back on the list of notes and we can see that the note has been updated.