To further demonstrate that Penny is still stone cold, such as can be used anywhere within our app.
Let's create a new page, a stats page, which actually we've already set up a page on a route for that.
On this page let's display a table which displays some information about our notes.
So we're going to display the total number of notes that we have and also the total number of characters
of all of our notes combined.
But before we set up this stats page, I've noticed that this mobile menu is not disappearing when we
click to go to a new page.
So let's just quickly fix that.
First number is in source component's layout number.
So let's scroll down to the script section.
So this show, Mobile NAV Ref is what is determining whether or not the mobile menu is shown.
So if I change this to true, we can see that the mobile menu is shown by default.
I'll set that back to false.
So what we could do is just make sure we set this back to false whenever one of our links in the mobile
menu is clicked.
So let's jump up to our route two links here notes.
And that's how we could just add a click handler to both of these.
So I'm going to do a multiple selection here, put my cursor here next to the word roots link, hold
down the alt key and then put another cursor next to this route to link opening tag enter.
I'm allowed to click color and we're just going to set this show mobile now back to false so we can
just to show mobile now equals false say that reload and hopefully this mobile menu will disappear when
we change pages on it does so let's use bonus table component to display some data about our notes.
So we'll just set up the mock up for that.
First, I'll close these files to our stats page source views, views that stop view.
So at a table with some nice styles, we just need to add a normal table with a class of table.
So let's create a table with a class of table and within that will add t head element and body element.
And then in our head element will add arrow so to our table row and within that will add a couple of
T cells, table heading cells.
And in the first one I'll just put the heading stat duplicate that and then in the second table heading,
I'll just put a value say that we can now see our table had a row that and that in our t body will add
a table row on inside that will add a couple of TDs table data cells.
In the first one we want to put the name of our stat, so I'm going to plot number of notes and then
in the second cell we're going to display the actual number of notes.
But for now I'll just put x, x, x and I'll duplicate this table row and then follow the name.
I'll put number of characters, parentheses of all notes, say that to make this table full width we
can just add a class to the table of is dash fold, dash width.
This is just another former class save, but actually I think full width is one word.
So let's get rid of that dash, save that.
And we now have a pretty decent looking table where we can display these stats.
So first, let's set up a getter for displaying the number of notes here.
So let's jump to our store file source stores, store notes.
JS So to get this at a comma and you get up so we could call this total notes count so are equal to
an arrow function pass in the state.
We want to return the total number of notes in our notes right in our state.
So to access our notes array we can do state of notes, so we can just return state start notes and
then to get the number of items in that array or the length of the you.
Right, we can just do dot length and save up.
So let's jump back to views.
That's the view that we need to import to store.
So let's set our script, set up text at a comment which says imports and we're going to import use
store notes from slush stores, lush store notes that we need to assign this to a constant create another
comment here underscore const store notes equals use store notes and we should now be able to use getter.
So let's replace this first x x x up to number of notes with double curly braces and store notes.
That's what did we call it, total notes count.
So store notes, the total notes count, save that.
And we now see that update two, two and we do have two notes.
If we add another note or maybe a couple more, jump back to the stats page.
This now says four.
So you can see that we can easily use everything that's in us to.
Anywhere within our app.
All of the data in our store and all of the results of our guesses are always kept up to date in real
time, regardless of where we go within our app.
So now let's set up one more getter for grabbing the number of characters of all notes, and that should
be number of characters.
Just change that.
So let's jump to a store again.
Add a new Gazza.
We'll call this one Total characters count.
Add an arrow function place in the state.
Now we're going to have to loop through every note that's in our notes array in order to figure out
the total number of characters of all notes.
So we could just set up a variable for counting this, or create a variable called count set that equal
to zero by default.
And then we'll just loop through our notes array, grab the length of the content from each one, and
then add that length to this count variable and then just return this count variable at the end.
So we could use a four each to do this.
So to grab our notes array, we can just do state dot notes that we can use a for each method to loop
through each note in this array.
And as it's looping through and it's looking at each one, we're going to need a placeholder.
So we'll just use note for that, then add an arrow function.
Okay.
So this is going to look at the first note and assign it to this note placeholder so we can just drop
the content.
Note content, notes dot content.
And then to get the length of that string, we can just do dot length.
So we can then just add the result of this to this count variable.
So we can just do count plus equals like that.
And then when it's done, looking at the first item, it'll jump to the second item and then grab the
length from this concept property and just keep adding to this count variable until it's gone completely
through the array so that at the end we can just return this count variable.
So let's just return counts.
Save that.
Reload the page.
Oh, we need to actually use this getter, which we've called total characters.
Count is going to copy that name job to use that stuff.
You select this x, x, x, add double curly braces and then to use our getter, we can just do store
notes, dots, total characters count, save that and we see the update.
And if we jump to the notes page edit one of our notes Joe back we could see this value is now increased
and if we delete all of our notes, jump to the stats page, we now see we have zero notes and zero
total characters.