We're going to spend the rest of this course taking everything we've learned to create this real world.
Note taking up called note balls.
Creating this app will allow us to take all of our new knowledge of the basics of the composition API
and solidify that knowledge with the creation of a real world app from scratch.
So in this app we can display a list of notes.
Each note has the notes on the number of characters and an edit and delete button.
We can add a new note.
And we can edit a note and save it.
We can delete a note as well with this confirmation model.
And we also have a header with links to our two pages, notes and stats.
And we have this stats page where we display stats related to our notes, including the number of notes
we have and the total number of characters of all our notes.
It's also going to look presentable, as you can see, by using the Boma CSS library, and it's also
going to be responsive as well.
So on desktop, we have these links to our two pages.
But if we scale this down, we can see all of the elements scaled out for mobile and our links in the
header changed to this little bigger icon.
Let me click on that.
Could see the links to our two pages.
This app is going to make use of almost every concept that we learned earlier on in the course, including
view routes on the use routes and use routes and posibles.
This time we're actually going to install the URL to set it all up from scratch.
It's going to use reactive data, including refs and reactive objects.
It's going to use methods, computed properties and watches.
It's going to use child components, including props limits and update model value.
It's going to use template refs on composable, including custom composable and a composable from the
view use library.
It's going to use directives and lifecycle hooks and we're going to set up all of our apps, state management
using Peneha.
Although this time we're actually going to install Peneha on set up our Peneha store completely from
scratch.
And of course, we'll also be adding state actions and a whole bunch of ghettoes to our Peneha store.