Let's create a brand new view.
Three projects for Note Balsa.
So let's jump on over to The View three website.
I'll search for View three and jump to the 3.5. org.
Earlier on in the course, I told you that the docs are about to be massively revamped and I had to
change the URL to get to the new docs.
But it looks like the new docs are now live.
So we can just jump to install gold now and again.
We need to have no jazz installed, but you probably already have that installed at this point.
So let's create a new view project with this command.
So I'll copy that jump to my terminal NPS code.
And again, we can toggle this with control and back to it.
I'll make sure you're in the folder way you stole your projects.
You definitely don't want to run this in the previous projects folder, if that's where you are.
So I'll paste that in and launch that and I'll type in Y to agree to install create view.
And for the project name and the project folder, I'm going to use view dash composition API Dash Note
False.
But you can use any folder name you like and I'm going to choose no to all of the options.
We're not going to install value out to this time because going to install that from scratch and set
it all up from scratch.
So no on again with pen.
Yeah, we're going to set that up from scratch.
So I'm going to choose no, no, no.
And you might want to consider using your own projects to help you ensure code quality.
But for simplicity, I'm just going to choose notes of this and we have some launch steps here.
So we just need to see into the folder and run NPM install to install the dependencies and then run
npm run dev and I can see the folder it's created here.
Composition API, no pulse.
So when to drag that into B code?
And then open up the terminal and ruin AMPM and store.
And then AMPM run dev to launch it.
Okay, now we can come on and click on this link.
We can see the basic hop running in the browser.
Before we get started, let's just change the name that is in the top there.
So I'm going to open up the explorer and go to index dot HTML.
I just changed the text in these title tags to note balls saved up.
We're now ready to get started creating note balls.