While there is an option in the bill to we just use to add the browser to our project automatically.
It's good to know how to do this manually, just in case you have to add browser to an existing view
three project which doesn't already have it set up.
So let's add the browser to our project and get it all set up.
So let's jump to our terminal and kill the dev process with control and say to install view out so we
can just run npm install view dash root at for.
Let's get the latest version of user.
And that's now installed so we can launch our project again with NPM, run dev, close the terminal
and see what the routes are to our app.
We need to jump to source and main.
Yes, we cannot be routed to our app by importing the create router method from view router and adding
it to this create chain with some options.
So first of all, after this first line, we need to import create router from view dash router and
we can now use this create router method to set up our router and we need to assign this to a constant.
So we'll create a constant called router and assign this to that.
We want to pass in an object here with all of our routes options.
On the first option we need to add is the history mode and we can set this to either create web history
or create web hash history.
Now create web history.
We'll use real URLs in the browser when we navigate across our pages.
So for example, if we went to an about page, then the path would just be about whereas with web hash
history, we will see slash, then hash, then slush, and then about when we go to our about page and
I'm going to use the web hash history here because when we're using this mode, we don't need any fancy
server setup to get our app running if we decide to deploy it to a server.
So let's set this history property to create web hash history.
And we need to import that from the user base code is automatically added that for me here.
But if yours hasn't, then just add it to this import.
On the next option we need to add is our roots.
So we create a property called routes.
Set that to an array and we can set up all of our routes in here.
But before we do that, let's add this router instance to our app.
So after this create app, we can add the use method to this chain.
Don't use parentheses, we can just pass in this route.
So constant.
I'm just going to break this up onto multiple lines and save that.
Let's make sure we're not seeing any errors.
I'll reload and I think this error might just be because we haven't set up any routes yet.
So let's do that next.