Let's set up some routes for our app and our app is going to have a notes view page and a stats view.
So let's set up a routes for our notes view first.
Well, first of all, we're going to need a component that we can use for that notes view.
So let's jump back to the File Explorer and we'll right click on the source folder.
I create a new folder called Views and this doesn't have to be called views.
You could call it pages if you like, but I'm going to call it views.
Let's create a new component in that I'm going to call this view notes dot view without template tags
on.
For now, I'll just add a div with a class of notes and inside that, a lot of each one that just says
notes.
Save that and we can now use this component for our notes view.
So let's jump back to Main.
Yes.
And add a route for our notes view.
For each route in our app, we need to add an object with some options.
First of all, we need the path option and this will determine what path will take us to this route.
I'm going to set the path to slash for the notes view, which just means this will be the route route
of our app.
So when we first visit our app.
This is the route that we'll go to.
Now, we also need to add a name property.
I'll set this to notes.
And this name property makes it easier for us to send the user to a particular route programmatically.
Finally, we need to add the component property, which we just set to the component that we want to
use for this route.
So first of all, we need to import our component.
So we'll import view notes from at slash views slash view notes dot view.
Now in previous view builds which used Webpack, we didn't need to put the top view here, but when
we're using beat, which we are now, we do need to add dot view and also this symbol here.
This is just an alias which refers to this source folder and this alias is being defined in this beta
dot config file.
We could see that here.
And you can also add your own aliases to different folders if you want to.
But anyway, let's jump back to Main as we can now set the component for this route.
So we'll set this to view notes.
Let's save that and reload.
We still have an error here and I've just figured out what the issue is when we set the history to create
web hash history.
This needs to be a method call, so we just need to add parentheses to the end of that.
Save that the app is now working again.
However, we can't see this notes view that we've just created in the browser, and that's because we
need to add a routes of view component to our app, to our route component app dot view.
I will do that in a minute, but before we do that, let's just set up a route for our stats page.
So let's jump back to the views folder and duplicate view notes dot view and we'll call this view stats
dot view.
I'll just change the class on the dev to stats and we'll change the text in the heading to stats as
well.
Save that jump back to Main.
Yes.
Let's add a comma after this route and duplicate that.
By the way, I did that by selecting this text and pressing alt shift and down and the shortcut might
be different on your platform.
Now let's get rid of this comma here and we'll set the path to slash stats so that when we go to slash
stats, we get to the stats view, we change the name to stats as well, and now we need to set the
component to our stats view.
But first we need to import it.
So I'll duplicate this Blue Notes line and we'll import view stats from slash view slash view stats
dot view and save that.
And we just need to change this component to view stats say that, but we still can't see our notes
view on the page.
If we go to the path slash and we can't see the stats view, if we go to the path slash stats and that's
because we need to add a root to view component to our app.
So let's do that next.