Let me go to the slush.
We don't see of you notes component with this heading with the tax notes.
And that's because we need to add a roots of view component to our app is the route to view component
which determines where our routes will be displayed.
So let's jump to our route component source update view.
I'm actually just going to remove the script section, remove everything inside the template and remove
the style tag and all of the styles as well.
Save that.
We can now also delete all of the components in the source components folder.
So I'll select everything in here.
Right click on Delete.
And we see an arrow, but if we reload than the error disappears.
So now to display our roots, we just need to add a roots view component.
And we can do this in a case like this.
Roots a dash view all we can do it in Pascal case, which I'm going to do so roots a view save that
we can now see our notes root on the page.
And if we go to the path slash stats, we can see us.
That's for you.
Now, using the address bar to navigate isn't much fun.
So let's add some roots link components to our page so that we can navigate.
So above this route to view component, I'm going to add a roots, a link component inside that output,
the text notes, and then I'll duplicate that.
In this one.
We've got the text stats to determine where these roots links will go.
We can just add a two prop and set it to the path we want to go to.
So for the notes, you can just set this to slash and then for the stats you can just set this to slash
stats.
So let's save that.
I'll just add a space after the first one and a pipe and then another space so that we can now navigate
around.