Our route is now all set up and working, but before we move on, let's just tidy up our code a little
bit.
So first of all, I'm just going to extract all of our router setup code into its own file.
So in the source folder, I'm going to create a new folder called Router in there I'm going to create
a new file called Index Dot.
Jess, let's jump back to Main JS and I'm going to use a multiple selection by holding down the alt
key, although the shortcut might be different on your platform.
When I select all of this route to contact the two imports for our notes view and stats view this line
where we're importing the create router and great web hash history methods from the router.
I'm going to cut all that and just tidy this up a little bit and then talk to index dot js in our roots
folder, paste all that code in.
I'll just add a line after our imports and now we want to export this router instance to make it available
to all the files.
So at the end we can just do export default router, save that.
Now if we jump back to Main, yes, we can import this router instance by adding import router from
us slash router and we don't actually need to add index docs when we use the file name.
Index dot just.
It will always look for this file automatically so we can just do import routes from other routes.
And now when we fire use routes, we're using the router instance from an index file in the router folder.
So let's say that.
See if everything is still working.
Yeah, it's all still working.
And one more thing.
I'm going to jump to index.
Yes.
And I'm going to put all of these routes into their own constant.
So I'm going to set up a constant called routes, set that equal to an array that I'm going to put these
two objects, paste those in here.
And now we can just set this routes, property to routes.
Or since these names are both the same, we could just shorthand this to just routes.
So let's save that.
Make sure it's still working and yet it's still working.
Now we've tidied up our main JS file and moved all of the code related to our routes into its own file.