Okay.
So our app is basically complete.
And in this app we've covered almost everything that we covered in the earlier modules.
It's just one more thing that I want to add, which is a modal that gets displayed when we click on
a delete button to prompt the user for confirmation before the note is deleted.
And the reasons I want to add this, number one, it will allow us to add a reactive object to our app,
which we haven't used yet.
Number two, it will allow us to use some lifecycle hooks which you haven't used yet.
And number three, it will help us to solidify our knowledge of data on events across parent and child
components using props limits on model value and update modal value.
And I think it's a good idea to go over this parent child stuff again, because these concepts can be
quite confusing, yet they're really key for creating solid composition API apps.
First, let's create a new component for our module.
So I'm going to jump to source components notes.
I'm going to create a new file in this folder called Modal.
Delete notes that view.
And for now, just going to stick our template tags in there on a Dave and I'll just put the text.
This is modal.
Save that now on our notes component note dot view.
Let's jump to that.
Components, notes and note here.
Let's add a reactive objects with a property for determining whether or not this modal is shown.
So I'm going to import ref from view.
So I'll add that here.
Then I'll scroll down to the bottom.
I'm going to add a block comment which says Models.
I'm going to set up a new reactive objects called models.
So const models equals reactive.
And actually it's reactive that we need to import from view, not ref.
So let's replace that with reactive passive in the object and I'm going to add a property called delete
note and set that equal to false on this property will determine whether or not the modal is shown.
So if it's false, we don't show it.
And if it's true, then we do show it on.
The reason I've used a reactive object here is because in a lot of apps like this, we might have a
bunch of different models.
So for example, right now when we edit note, we dropped to a new page, but we might decide to replace
this functionality with a modal for editing the notes.
And so this reactive object gives us a place where we can manage all of our models together.
So we might have another property here, edit notes model and then use this to manage.
Edit Notes Modal.
But for now we're just going to add this delete notes modal.
So I'll get rid of that and save that.
Okay, so let's import our new modal component and only display it when this delete notes property is
true.
So we'll jump to our imports and we're going to import modal delete notes from at slush components slash
notes slash modal delete note stop view.
I'll save that.
And now let's place this after our footer element.
So modal delete note save that.
We can now see that on both of our notes.
But let's only display this when models dot delete notes is true.
So a lot of the if directive to this modal fake dash if models dot's delete note save that and we see
the modal disappear and if we change modal start delete note to true, then we see it reappear.
Let's set that back to false and save that.
Okay, now let's use Bulma to create a nice looking modal.
So let's jump back to the BOMA site.
Omega IO docs two components and modal.
Let's scroll down a bit here and we're going to use this modal card example, which looks pretty nice.
So I'm going to copy all of the code for this and jump to modal delete note dot view.
Just paste all of that in here.
Get rid of the Dave that we added before, indent it all a bit on, save, reload and so that we can
actually see this modal when we click on Delete.
Let's jump to our delete button on note dot view, which is here and instead of triggering odd delete
note action in our store.
We'll instead just show this model.
So to do this we can just do models.
Dot delete notes.
Equals true.
Save that.
Click on delete and we're still not seeing the model.
Let's see if it's being added to our markup here.
So I'll inspect this note and we can see the model has been added to the page, but we're not seeing
it.
And I think that's because we need to add a class of is active to the modal now we can see it.
So let's jump back to our modal component and add this class to the route.
If is dash active, save that.
Now let's click on a delete button and we can now see the modal.
So now let's modify this a bit.
Let's change this title here.
Modal title to delete note question mark save that.
Let's add some content to the body here.
So inside this modal body class, we'll just add are you sure you want to delete this note?
Save that and we can now see that message.
Now I want to align these buttons over to the right.
And if we jump to this footer element with a class of modal dash car dash four, we can do this by adding
one of Bowman's Flexbox classes, which is is dash justify dash content dash items dash and save that
actually I think it's is justified content flex and let's try that save that on again you can find all
of these classes documented on the board mosaic okay, now I'm going to swap these buttons around.
I put the council button first inside this footer and I'm going to change the text in this save changes
button to delete.
And I think it makes sense to make this button red so we can just change.
This is success.
Class two is danger to make it red.
Okay, this modal is looking pretty good now.
Now we just need to get it behaving correctly so that, number one, we can hide it when we click on
this X or the council button or if we click outside of the model to do that, we're going to use our
click site composable from view use again.
And we also need to get this to actually delete the note when we click on the delete button.
I'm also going to add some keyboard control to this so that the user can hit escape to close the model.
To do that, we're going to make use of some lifecycle hooks.