So if the user clicks on this cancel button, all this X button, then we want to hide this modal.
Now these buttons are in our child component modal to the note dot view.
But if the user clicks these buttons, then we want to modify the models dot delete note property,
which is on the parent component.
And one way we could do this is by emitting a custom event.
Let me click on these buttons and then in the parent component note dot view listening out.
For that event and when it's received.
Set models dot delete note but to false.
However, as we learned earlier in the course, we don't actually need to do this.
We can get a child component.
To directly modify a data property which is on its parent component by passing this reactive data property
down to the child component using V model, then receiving the value of the model, using the special
model value prop and then updating the source of that model value on the parent component by using update
model value.
Well, first of all, let's pass down model's dot delete note to the child component using V model.
So let's jump up to our model delete note component here.
I'm allowed a V model directive and set that to the same as the V.
If so, models dot delete note paste that in there save that we can now receive this v model using the
special model value prop on the child component.
So let's jump to model delete note view at the script section on the setup attribute and the sets of
props.
So a lot of comment here which says props.
I'm a lot of constant call props set by equal to the define props method percent and object.
I will define our props here.
So to receive this data property that we're passing down with V model, we need to use the model value
prop set that equal to an object.
The type is going to be boolean because models up to the know is a billion.
It's only going to be true or false.
I we'll set the default to false and save that.
And to make sure this is being passed down correctly and received correctly, let's just output this
model value prop in our template.
So after the text that we added to the body without a pre tag and just output double curly braces and
model value, save that, I'll just reload the app, click on delete and yeah, we can see that's going
through because we can see true here.
Now let's just remove this pre tuck and save that.
Now let's create a method that can be fired when we click on the x button or the console button.
So let's jump down to the script section in modal delete note dot view on a section called Close Modal
and I'll create a constant called Close Modal set that equal to an arrow function.
And for now we'll just log out Close Modal, save that.
Now let's trigger this method on buttons.
So the council button is going to break this up onto multiple lines.
Split the attributes I'm allowed to click on the UT Click Equals Close Modal.
Then I'm going to copy this.
Click on let find this little button.
Where is that thing?
Oh, here it is.
I'll split that onto multiple lines and split the attributes I'm just paste in that click on.
Let say that unless make sure this close modal method is firing.
Click on the console button.
We see the lock click on the X button and we see the log.
So now we just need to omit the update model value event in this method.
So first of all, we need to define our omits.
So let's order omits section create a constant called omit set that equal to the defined limits method,
pass in an array and we'll just add the updates called on modal value.
Save that and we can now omit this special event.
So in our closed modal method we can just to omit and then.
Update model value.
So this is going to change the source data property in the parent component that we're passing down
with the model and receiving with model value.
So it's going to update this delete note property in the parent component note dot view.
So we need to tell it what value to set it to and we want to hide the modal.
So we want to set this back to false.
So let's jump down to this emit.
We can just add false as a second parameter.
Let's save that and see if it's working.
Show the delete model.
Click on the X and that's working.
Click on Cancel and that's working as well.