It would be better if this modal closed itself.
If we clicked anywhere outside of the card.
That's the kind of functionality we would expect from a modal like this.
And remember, we used that outside composable earlier from view use to make this mobile nav menu disappear
when we click outside of it.
So we could use that again here.
But before we do that, I don't like the fact that there's no putting around this model when we're on
a smaller screen.
Get a lot better with a little bit putting.
So this started with the class of modal.
This kind of class of pay us to.
To give that a little bit padding that looks a bit better, I think.
Okay, so let's use that.
Click outside composable here so that we can close this modal when we click outside of the card.
So I want to jump to the Explorer.
I'm just going to right click the source folder and choose find in folder and search for click outside
and there is it on up.
So let's jump to that.
So I'm going to copy this import and then jump to modal delete now dot view and add this to the top.
So imports paste that there.
Jump back to you, not part of you.
Now let's copy all of this code.
We might as well copy the comment as well and jump back to delete modal.
I will paste this at the bottom.
So remember we need a template ref.
To tell this composable which element we're going to be clicking outside of.
To then do something.
So let's replace this snap menu here and here with what we're going to be clicking outside of this modal
dash card diff.
So we could call this modal card ref.
And then let's add this to the modal card.
Split the attributes of this ref, modal card ref.
Save the.
And I don't think we're going to need this ignore option.
So I'm just going to remove.
This third parameter, this object and this comma as well.
Like that.
And we can get rid of this data ref, which we were adding to that ignore option.
Now, when we do click outside, we just want to hide the modal by triggering this.
Method close modal so we can actually just select all of this, handle the hair from the closing curly
brace to these parentheses.
I just put the name of method close modal.
So let's save that.
See if that's working.
Reload show the modal and we have an error here.
Ref is not defined.
I guess we need to import the ref method from view.
So import ref from view.
Save that reload.
Show the modal click outside on.
Yeah, it's working.
Let's just make sure it's not being triggered erroneously like it was on the knop before.
Yeah.
It only gets fired if we click right outside of the card and the console and x buttons are still working.