We usually expect to be able to close a motel like this by hitting the escape key on our keyboard.
So let's set up some keyboard handling in the mounted hook of this modal delete note w component.
So I'm going to jump to modal delete note W on down to the bottom and I'll create a comment called Keyboard
Control.
I'm a lot and on mount it took.
Toss in a handler to that like that and we'll just log out on mount it for now.
Say that we have an error here on Mount.
It is not defined.
Find us because we need to import this lifecycle from view so that's out it on mounted save that reload
show the modal I can see on mount it being locked out and if we hide it and show it again we can say
on Mount it is locked out again.
So now inside our mounted hook, let's set up an event listener for the key event.
Which will be fired after we press key and then let go of it.
So let's get rid of this lock and we can just do document, dot, add event listener parentheses and
then follow the first parameter.
This is the event we're going to listen out for and we're going to listen out for the key event.
And the second parameter is our handler.
So let's add an arrow function here and let's also passing the event object.
I'll replace these parentheses with an E and then we'll just lock that out for now.
So console log a save that and reload show a modal and hit the escape key and we can see the keyboard
event being locked out there.
Within this event object, we can see that when we hit the escape key, this key property is set to
escape and this key property is generally the property that we want to check in our JavaScript to determine
which.
Key was pressed.
So let's check if the escape key was pressed.
And if so, then we can just fire a closed modal method, thus hiding the modal.
So let's remove this console lock and we can just do f e dot.
Key is equal to escape.
Then you can just fire the close modal method and save that.
Reload.
Show the moto and hit the escape key.
And that's working.
We see the modal disappear.
However, we do have an issue here.
If we look something out inside this event.
Listener.
We could just log out, close it.
Save that and if I reload, click on delete to show the modal and hit escape.
Then we see close it being locked out once.
But if I show another modal on here escape, it's now been logged out twice this time.
And if we show a modal again and hit escape this time it's been locked out three times.
And this is because even after the modal is closed, this event listener still exists.
This event listener is not being removed when we close the modal.
So when we first show a modal, this event listener is set up.
Then we closed the motel.
This is still sets up.
Then we open another motel and we then sets up a second event list.
Now.
So at this point, we now have two of these event listeners firing and it will keep adding a new event
list every time we show a new model.
So what we need to do is remove this event listener when the model is closed and we can do this in the
on mounted hook, which will be fired when our model is removed from the domain.
Now, first, to make an event listener removable, we need to put its callback function into its own
named function.
So both are mounted hook.
I'm going to create a constant called handle keyboard set equal to an arrow function in the eight parameter
the event object.
Now I'm going to cut these two lines.
I'm paste them into this new function.
And now we can just select all of this handler from the closing curly brace.
Up to the age.
I'm just passing in the name of this function handle keyboard.
So let's save that and make sure that's still working.
Hit the escape gate.
And yet that's still working.
So now we just need to remove this event list, not in the on mounted hook.
So after the on mounted hook will harden on on mounted hook percent arrow function handler.
Now to remove this event list, now we can just use the remove event list.
No method.
So I'm just going to copy all of this line paste line here and change out event list not to remove event
list to save that.
And we do need to add the on on mounted hook to our imports.
So let's add that here on on.
Mounted.
Save that.
Now let's see if this is working.
So click the delete button.
Show the model here.
Escape.
And we see our log being fired only once.
Click Delete again show the moto hit escape and we now see close it only being logged out once again.
So this is not working.
That event last night is being removed when the modal is closed and if we keep it an escape here, we
don't see anything locked out.
So we can now just remove that console.log from the handle keyboard function saved up.
And now all we need to do is delete this sucker when the user clicks on delete in the modal.