The final thing we need to do is actually delete the notes that the user's trying to delete when they
click on this read to report it.
Now we already have a delete note action in our store and source stores and store notes such as due
to the actions we already have this delete note action set up which we can use to delete the notes and
all this action is expecting is the ID of the note that we want to delete so we can just trigger this
action directly in our modal delete note w component.
So let's jump to that and so on the delete button which is here, we just want to trigger that action
in our store.
Delete note and that's expecting an ID, but we don't actually have access to the note ID within this
component.
However, if we jump to its parent component note view, then we do have access to all of the note information
here in this note prop.
So we could use this to pass the notes ID down to the child component modal to the note up view using
a prop.
So let's jump up to our modal delete note component which is here.
And we could either pass down the entire note object so we could call this note set about equal to notes.
And this would pass down the entire object with both the ID and the content.
However, we only actually need the ID so we might as well only pass the ID down.
So to do that, we could pass down notes ID and maybe just change the name of the prop to note I.D.
Camel case and save that.
So now we need to receive this notes ID prop.
In the modal delete note dot view component.
So let's jump to that, jump to our props.
I'm allowed this prop here.
So notes ID type is going to be string.
I will make this required as well, so I'll set required to trigger.
So let's save that.
Make sure this note's ID prop is getting through.
So after content here in the modal, let's just output a pre tag with double carry braces and note I'd
save the reload and show the modal and yeah we could see ID one being spits out for the first note,
an ID to being spits out for the second note.
So let's get rid of this pre tuck and we now just need to import store our opinion store into this modal
component and just trigger this delete note action and pass in the ID.
So first we need to import it.
So we can just do import use store notes from slash stores.
Slash use store.
Actually, no, that's at slash stores.
Slash store notes say that we need to assign this store to a constant.
So after our props and limits, let's add a store comment and just do const store notes equals use store
notes parentheses save that we should now have access to our store here.
And this delete note action within the store.
So let's jump up to the delete button which is here and I'll split this up onto multiple lines and split
the attributes onto multiple lines at a click color.
We just want to fire the delete note action that's in our store so we can just do store notes, thoughts,
delete notes on passing the ID day on again.
We're passing down the ID in this note ID so we can just do store notes, delete notes, notes ID.
Let's save that and see if it's working.
Reload.
Click on Delete.
Click on Delete again and we can see the note was deleted and we can also see that the modal is being
hidden automatically as well when we click delete.
And that's because the modal is a child component of note dot view.
A note dot view is the component we're using to display the note.
So when we delete a note.
That no view component gets removed from the dump along with all of its child components, including
modal delete note dot view component.